<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/4.9.1" created="2017-12-17 05:33" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Microsoft World</title>
	<link>http://msftworld.ml</link>
	<description>Microsoft News &#38; Analysis</description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 05:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://msftworld.ml</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://msftworld.ml</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login><![CDATA[revben]]></wp:author_login><wp:author_email><![CDATA[revibennett@outlook.com]]></wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[revben]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/cropped-aLogomakr_7YkbOo-Copy.pngcccc-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Microsoft World</title>
	<link>http://msftworld.ml</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 

	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/12/hello-world__trashed/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msftworld.ml/?p=1</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>1</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:34:52]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:34:52]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[hello-world__trashed]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[trash]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_time]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512487903]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_status]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_desired_post_slug]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[hello-world]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_comments_status]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:1;s:1:"1";}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>1</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[A WordPress Commenter]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email><![CDATA[wapuu@wordpress.example]]></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url>https://wordpress.org/</wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:34:52]]></wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:34:52]]></wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi, this is a comment.
To get started with moderating, editing, and deleting comments, please visit the Comments screen in the dashboard.
Commenter avatars come from <a href="https://gravatar.com">Gravatar</a>.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved><![CDATA[post-trashed]]></wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>0</wp:comment_user_id>
		</wp:comment>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The World of Office 365</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/12/the-world-of-office-365/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 14:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msftworld.ml/?p=5</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3> Office 365 Is A Star</h3>
Office 365 is Microsoft’s most important business. Office 365 has quickly grown to a multi-billion dollars per quarter business and it is still growing in the high double digits and the future runway is straight, long and clear. Office 365 is also a very complex business. I will try to break it down in this post.
<h3>Office 365 Components</h3>
<h4>Word</h4>
Word is Microsoft's trusty word processing program. It is one of the most important and popular programs Microsoft has.
<h4>PowerPoint</h4>
The second most popular program in Microsoft Office, PowerPoint, is Microsoft’s iconic presentation program, that many in college and high school are very familiar with.
<h4>Excel</h4>
The third program is the triad, Excel is probably the most irreplaceable program in the Office Suite. Excel is a spreadsheet program that can calculate anything and host unlimited data.
<h4>Outlook</h4>
Outlook is a desktop email program that is the most used email client in the Enterprise and it is not even close.
<h4>Access</h4>
A magnificent database management system application.
<h4>Publisher</h4>
This a program used for designing brochures, labels, calendars, greeting cards, business cards, newsletters, websites, and postcards.
<h4>OneNote</h4>
OneNote is a notetaking program that gathers handwritten or typed notes, drawings, screen clippings and audio commentaries.
<h4>Project</h4>
Project is a project management application for Windows to keep track of events and to create network charts and Gantt charts.
<h4>Visio</h4>
Visio is diagram and flowcharting app for Windows.
<h4>Skype For Business</h4>
This Microsoft one of Microsoft’s unified communication platform and it is one of the leaders in this technology sector.
<h4>Microsoft Team</h4>
Microsoft’s newest unified communication platform that was made in response to Slack. It has been so successfully rolled-out that Microsoft will replace Skype For Business with it.
<h4>OneDrive For Business</h4>
This Microsoft’s cloud storage platform for business that offers 1TB per user in Office 365.
<h4>SharePoint</h4>
SharePoint allows you to share and manage content, knowledge, and applications to empower teamwork, quickly find information, and seamlessly collaborate across the organization.
<h4>Office Online</h4>
• Word Online: Free web app version of Microsoft Word.
• Excel Online: Free web app version of Microsoft Excel.
• PowerPoint Online: Free web app version of Microsoft PowerPoint.
• OneNote Online: Free web app version of Microsoft OneNote.
<h4>Delve</h4>
Delve allows Office 365 users to search and manage their emails, meetings, contacts, social networks and documents stored on OneDrive or Sites in Office 365.
<h4>Office Forms</h4>
This an online survey creator.
<h4>Outlook Web App</h4>
A comprehensive online email client that only comes through Office 365 plans or Microsoft Exchange server.
<h4>Microsoft Planner</h4>
This a planning application.
<h4>Office 365 Video</h4>
A video sharing service in some Office 365 plans.
<h4>Bookings</h4>
Bookings in an appointment booking application on the Microsoft Office 365 platform.
<h3>Office 365 Plans</h3>
There are four main categories of Office 365 plans: Business, Enterprise, Education and Home. Other types of plans include: Nonprofit, Government, and Firstline Workers
<h3>Enterprise Plans</h3>
<h4>ProPlus</h4>
This is a plan with just the desktop Office applications. There are no online services included, except OneDrive for Business. It also comes with the desktop client for Skype for Business. It costs $12/user/month for unlimited users.
<h4>E1</h4>
This is the unlimited user Office 365 plan that comes with only Office 365 online services. The services include Skype for Business, Exchange (Outlook), Office Online and Microsoft Team. It will cost $8/user/month.
<h4>E3</h4>
This is a combination of E1 and ProPlus for $20/user/month. It also has security and compliance tools, such as legal hold and data loss prevention. A company can have an unlimited amount of users on this plan.
<h4>E5</h4>
This is the granddaddy of Office 365 plans. It encompasses all the services that Microsoft offers. It also has some exclusive services such as Power BI Pro, Advanced Threat Detection, Customer Lockbox-to control accesses to Outlook mailbox, Advanced Data Governance, Office 365 Cloud App Security and Advanced Voice Capabilities. It cost $35/user/month. A company on this plan has unlimited user capacity.
<h3>Business Plan</h3>
<h4>Business Essentials</h4>
This is the basic Small business plan. It comes with the online services of Office 365. It costs 5/user/month and it is limited to 300 users.
<h4>Business</h4>
This is a plan that contains the Office desktop applications that will cost $8.50/user/month. It is also limited to 300 users. It does not offer any online service barring OneDrive for Business.
<h4>Business Premium</h4>
This is a combination of Business and Business Essentials that costs $12.50/user/month. A small business can place 300 employees on this plan.
<h3>Education Plans</h3>
<h4>A1</h4>
This is a free Office 365 plan includes the Office 365 online services. It also contains School Data Sync which is a service that reads the school and roster data from a school's Student Information System.
<h4>A3</h4>
A3 contains all the features in A1 in addition to full access to the Office desktop apps. It also comes with additional management and security tool. It costs $2.5/month for student and $3.25/month for faculty and staff members.
<h4>A5</h4>
This is the most comprehensive Office 365 Education Plan that has all the features available in A3. It comes with Microsoft’s best-in-class intelligent security management, advanced compliance, and analytics systems. It costs students $6/user/month and $8/user/month for faculty and staff members.
<h3>Home Plans</h3>
There are two plans. Office 365 Personal which grants the user 1 license to the PC or Mac version of Office desktop applications that include: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, OneNote, and Outlook. It also comes with 1tb of OneDrive storage. It also grants 60 minute of Skype calls per month to mobile phones and landlines. The other Home plan is just called Home. It has all the features of Personal except it grants a license to up to 5 users and each those users are granted 1tb of storage and 60 minutes per month.
<h3>Government Plans</h3>
<h4>U.S. Government Community G5</h4>
This is a Government plan that contains Office 365 U.S. Government Community G3. In addition, to the desktop applications, it also provides unified communications with Skype for Business Server, advanced eDiscovery with predictive coding and text analytics, Exchange Online Advanced Threat Protection, personal and organizational analytics, Audio Conferencing, and other services.
<h4>U.S. Government Community G3</h4>
G3 contains Office 365 U.S. Government Community G1 plus Office desktop applications, personalized search and discovery, self-service business intelligence, enterprise management of apps, eDiscovery tools, hosted voicemail with auto-attendant capabilities, and other services.
<h4>U.S. Government Community G1</h4>
This is a Government plan that contains a subset of Office 365 online services.
<h3>Nonprofit</h3>
These plans are just reduced-price Business and Enterprise plans. The new pricing is:
• Business Essential- Donation
• Business Premium- $2/user/month
• Enterprise E1-Donation
• Enterprise E3- $4.50/user/month
• Enterprise E5- $10/user/month

It is easy to see that Office 365 has a wide range of options for all size business. Its expansive sets of plans are working, given that it has 120 million monthly active users. However, it does have a lot of completion. Some of the completion are:
<h3>Google G-Suite</h3>
This is the biggest competition to Office 365 and Office in general. G Suite comprises Gmail, Hangouts, Calendar, Google+, Drive, Docs, Sheets, Slides, Forms, Sites. There is also an Admin panel and Vault for managing users and the services.
<ul>
 	<li>Gmail: Online email service.</li>
 	<li>Hangouts: Googles unified communication platform, that was born online.</li>
 	<li>Calendar: Calendar service attached to each G Suite user.</li>
 	<li>Google +: Google’s take on Enterprise social network.</li>
 	<li>Drive: Google’s online storage service.</li>
 	<li>Docs: Word processor that popularized online co-authoring.</li>
 	<li>Sheets: A spreadsheet companion to Docs that also has rich collaboration tools.</li>
 	<li>Slides: The presentation arm of Google’s productivity services.</li>
 	<li>Forms: A survey and quiz making service by Google.</li>
 	<li>Sites: This is a tool that allows users to create websites without knowing how to code.</li>
 	<li>Keep: A note-taking service from Google.</li>
</ul>
<h4>Pricing</h4>
Google G-Suite is known for its cheap pricing plans. The plans are Basic which is for $5/user/month that provides all the services above with 30 GB of cloud storage. The next plan Business for $10/user/month. It offers unlimited storage unless there are less than 5 users on the plan. The last plan is Enterprise that offers everything in the Business plan plus security and other enterprise-focused services. It costs $25/user/month. All these plans are offered to unlimited users.
<h4>Comparison</h4>
There are no like for like Office 365 and G-Suite plans, so a direct comparison is not possible. The closest plans are the E1 to Google Business plan and E3 to Google Enterprise plan. The E1 and Business plans offer very similar services, however, the E1 is cheaper. However, the Business plan offers unlimited storage if there are more than 5 users. This makes them awash. However, when comparing the Enterprise and E3 plans, it is clear to see that the E1 offers more for less when you take into account that it is cheaper while offering the same services with the addition of the desktop versions of Office, on up to five PCs.
Despite, the reputation of Suite being cheap for business, it is no cheaper than Office 365.
<h3>Zoho Office Suite</h3>
Zoho Office Suite is a SaaS office suite containing word processing, spreadsheets, presentations, databases, note-taking, CRM, project management, invoicing and other applications developed by Zoho Corporation. Zoho Office Suite is free to use at the basic level, but require payment for more complex features.
<ul>
 	<li>Zoho Writer: The suite's word processor supports simultaneous collaboration between multiple users.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Sheet: Sheet is the spreadsheet application in the suite.</li>
 	<li>Zoho DB and Reports: An online database and reporting application in the suite.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Show: This is the presentation program in the suite.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Projects: Zoho Projects supports creating tasks, assigning ownership, setting deadlines and tracking milestones.</li>
 	<li>Zoho CRM: This is a customer relationship management application.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Creator: A database/custom application development tool which allows users to create process logic by dragging &amp; dropping script elements on screen, without knowing code.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Wiki: Allows users to create their own website.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Discussions: Create external and internal communities where problems are solved, topics are discussed, and ideas are exchanged.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Planner: An online planner with a calendar, to-do lists, pages, and e-mail reminders.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Notebook: A notetaking application.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Chat: A chat application that can be embedded into pages or blogs.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Mail: This is web-based email application.</li>
 	<li>Zoho Meeting: A web conference application.</li>
 	<li>Zoho People: On-Demand HRIS &amp; Applicant Tracking System.</li>
</ul>
Zoho Office Suite main plan is called One. It can be had for $35/user/month billed monthly or $30/user/month billed annually. One is the all-in-one platform from Zoho, that offers everything for one price and one interfere. It is similar to Office 365 in the way it is implemented. It defers from Office 365 because it has only one plan and it offers Customer Relationship Management and Financial applications in the package. Each component can be bought individually, and each has a free option.

It compares very to Office 365. I really love what they are doing. That is why I argue that it should be one of the companies Microsoft should buy next.
<h3>Quip</h3>
Quip is a collaborative productive service that is currently owned by Salesforce.com. The core of Quip provides word processing and spreadsheet functionality, accessible via the Web, an iOS app, and an Android app. Alongside all documents on Quip is a live updating history of edits made, as well as the ability to highlight portions of a document and add comments, which facilitates collaboration. Quip also has a chat based communication platform as well as what they call Live Apps, which are apps that gives additional functionality to the core platform.

It also has tight integration with Salesforce.com and other productivity platforms such as Google G-Suite.
It can be had for $30/month for the first five users, with an additional $10 needed for each additional user when billed monthly and $12 when billed yearly. There is also an enterprise plan that comes with the usual enterprise-focused plans such as added security and compliance tools. It will cost a company 25/user/month

On its own, it was not a real threat to Office 365, but given that it has been bought by Salesforce.com, it has become a bigger threat. It no longer has to worry about making a profit and it will be pushed by one of the top SaaS companies in the world.

[maxbutton id="1" ]

[amazon_link asins='B00B1TEIRU,B0148BYIAO,B01606IDL0,B01606KJ6C,B0727VQLGM,B0727VQK39,B0163GNS5S,B07193J237' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='b2580c71-da46-11e7-a8db-c7e2c3a07a6b']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>5</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:50:20]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:50:20]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-world-of-office-365]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="cloud-services"><![CDATA[Cloud Services]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="office-365"><![CDATA[Office 365]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_121f1152e8697d7ae6189bbe0fb8a707]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3700b285fdbe16a63d520b5d2b03a193]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8086781fdb517462ae3be0affbd26c72]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f5ad919e8e815d8123b4ede20eb6fa85]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_af459ebf0c8024c2c0e091c40c151e2f]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_16789cc527ea844595f2fa6afca0eb7d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_ee91b7e2504a17934798049b78283bdd]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9be79a6db79182673618505a168c101c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_de89ceb64e340861053da5d585f2e8ad]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_fc9d49c980ba8fcc5a33cff936229eb1]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f431ecfe6e88f40dab9c375a6c422f5b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d827ef185ba9205e56ca4e02d971bb72]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c38b0056087089a69f1e7a17072bf410]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3258b56ae5195f8456b35d4211cd97eb]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6330689294]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2a496a3bd21ae7148edae6417cc20da4]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5445c133035f300eb1d413a6137b33c9]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_cc82848e0e4cc8b16fb0e4f500e9fe0e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_99d6a2d6aa31237ba888a33e7f302b09]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8e8246b5e7065e43540259d3032e1257]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_49940b5de598a2ff497abb5f057b6fdc]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5a8d3e03ea099fe5b66020b962b37b08]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_cf1efe777137ffa5002048116e8e1203]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e93a1b2ff38785e72616bbc82b13e43d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_bc7f8a87ce1a6aa3383ddf5880186fc5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3c13b68889ecda8a7fe2d670a66d5796]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9b83c6324e9aa12434d71fd5922416d0]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4e828fc7bee476728f530638c65499e9]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3d1d0ae4adebfc0bc270690f6549ba14]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9069c11de8434a263b4c70a6009547c9]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_516c7e67005fa1a83bc17e801f82e1a2]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0e4a3fd515658ede93dbdbb19b1ab069]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d068c5c36657a54f408bbc08702f8575]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1fd722a96a6a318684b9a18c70d01fd3]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_dae0fa9a26094ede9dc2fb04006cbf1d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_b90ec5352e4b7b5f45be39091226cae2]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_b0d67d51d2c9f6f2e8e23fc64efa6f06]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9108630bd0e24c8ece5c9e83a2238b97]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2a37d6a820533e10668c75ccf558a006]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_21711e9e9be4af55d315ccf61a81f4f5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_073f8e149860606777db8aa8d4c95025]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2df84a04bd8c937bd00f278630493212]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_41348ae692c86345b278fcdc5f7086fb]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_894dde761d6b19969b46425118c309f1]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_fcba884c261a867723298b2f7b125bd2]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6c3c3df3a9d1c0f0bb03feddaaf8af5b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d5a7a01f01cf04bfe0f6c514ca68d05d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c2a7f49821ac291765468301f17443a4]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_bc3d231a47bd94ad1c04bc35a667fd5c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a2992906c234f8f4ccf779daa6e09e6c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2b0d07f7dec88a57f6d1dcf392fc4c88]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3dac85e7aeae698add6105e1190ee738]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_dfc3ae242ce2c3326e900d110d11635d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1aeebab2643af216b0ced8ca6ebd9ef5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6aa62c0e8c897f0bf063f39ff2bd6669]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_93f272a5a29e5bd4be23fa86f52a6eae]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_75fa5a408ecda69d381ae9933b8c4be3]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2da74c8e5a39422af01a1180449fc18a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_fd5f0369c4e98acb6fb48c084501e65e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_831accf73cccce636a03b95468dc22bb]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4e516d2b0ad7aea3338035da95f071d8]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2d71bc6ae6e24a9f210693a267fe508f]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a3e12d3e07381ef96ae4a8f1b4734cc9]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_cb9bae75ad3ae43482ff79d743e49747]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a66ff4d76c2f304f25edef6dd21e8f82]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1f2da8a7b64d76b2c190bc5d4b1c1052]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2ef4836a770993d8fbbaea54079b423c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_30e40b93fba10d46673d109f5f91d580]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_ce4a6ec70dc34991afa767a4707994dd]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4a596e55187de8bcc0b550c008b40512]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_794f667f0e17984aa2152040bcfedc93]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[48]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f7a0ad1c592a0d499b0ea826c5dcd868]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[flash_page_layout]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default-layout]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[30]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Who Should Microsoft Buy Next?</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/12/who-should-microsoft-buy-next/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 14:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msftworld.ml/?p=7</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Microsoft Loves To Buy</h3>
Microsoft is a company with a penchant for acquiring other technology company. Most of their acquisitions have been in the software realm. Therefore, any purchase going forward is most likely going to be of another software company. Let us explore some companies that could easily become a part of the Microsoft family within the next three years.

The potential acquisitions will be placed in four categories. The first one is Just A Matter of Time, followed by Massive But Expected, Shake Up The Tech World and the last category is Others.
<h3>Just A Matter of Time</h3>
These are possible acquisitions that seem very likely. In fact, some in the tech community might be wondering how Microsoft or another tech powerhouse has not brought them yet.
<h4>Zoho Cooperation</h4>
Zoho is enterprise software and service company located in India. They have three brands; Zoho, ManageEngine, WebNMS. Zoho itself has many productivity products, too many to name. Every product that Microsoft has in its productivity arsenal, Zoho has also. It newest product Zoho One is described as an “operating system for your business”. It packs in CRM, Mail, Books-accounting software, Creator-for custom apps and Sprints-for planning and tracking projects.

ManageEngine is an IT management software that Zoho claims is used by 3 out 5 Fortune 500 companies. WebNMS is their IoT platform; this was actually the founding project of Zoho when it was formed in 1996 as AdventNet. Zoho is a private company that does not raise capital nor intents to have an IPO. It says that it is consistently profitable, but its revenue and profit is not known. Its market capitalization is also not known.

Whatever, its worth, I am sure Microsoft can easily afford it. Microsoft does not need Zoho, but it could be a good fit for Microsoft. It is an Asian company and the Asian market has always been hard to penetrate by western companies. Zoho could help Microsoft further establish Office 365 and Dynamics 365 in the Asian market especially India and China.
<h4>Workday</h4>
Workday was formed in 2005 by Aneel Bhusri and Dave Duffield to provide cloud-based applications in finance and Human Resource. Their products are Financial Management, Financial Performance Management, Human Capital Management, Prism Analytics and Professional Services Automation. It has more than 700 enterprise customers worldwide in 2015 and more than 7, 400 employees in 2017. In its latest quarterly report for May to July 2017, it reported revenue of 525.3 million dollars on a net loss of 81.6 million dollars. It has a market capitalization of 24 billion dollars. It is on the expensive side, but it has great market value.

If Microsoft were to buy Workday, it would not have to be too worried about the loss, given that most of it is through research and development and sales and marketing. Those would be lessened over time as it absorbed into Microsoft other cloud services. Microsoft would be gaining one of the top enterprise software start-ups around as well as a greater foothold into the Human Resources and Finance Management software sector. Workday would fit seamlessly into Dynamics 365.
<h4>Tableau</h4>
Tableau is a Data Visualization company that use Business Intelligence to turn complex data into visually rich presentations. It is like Microsoft Power BI apps. However, Tableau is not profitable nor is growing at a pace that can justify the continued losses. In its latest quarterly report, it had a revenue increase of 4% to $214.9 million dollars. Net loss for the third quarter of 2017 was $46.6 million.
Having total revenue of 215 million and only growing by 4% and having 46.6 million dollars in losses is not the best financial picture. With a market value of 5.6 billion dollars, Microsoft could force a sale if it wanted. Power BI has been putting pressure on Tableau, therefore, it would probably be in its best interest to sell. Microsoft would be the best company to sell to.
<h4>LogMeIn Inc</h4>
LogMeIn is a Software as a Service (SaaS) that has interest in many areas. It most popular products are LastPass and GoTo, both of which it gained through acquisitions. GoTo most popular product is GoToMeeting, which is an online meeting SaaS. LastPass is a password management software. It also has many consumer support services like Rescue and GoToAssist.

LogMeIn is worth 6.2 billion dollars. In its latest quarterly earnings report, it reported revenue of 270 million dollars and net income of 10 million dollars. It does not have the highest revenue in the world, but its revenue is profitable. Microsoft could buy it to lessen the competition on Skype for Business/Microsoft Team by GoToMeeting. GoToMeeting would come with its own technology and customers. There are many other products and services that Microsoft would get from LogMeIn, that Microsoft could throw in Office 365 and Dynamics 365. Paying around 7 billion dollars for a profitable competitor is always good business.
<h3>Massive But Expected</h3>
These are massive companies that Microsoft have a great relationship and fit well into Microsoft’s existing enterprise offerings. Though these are massive and profitable companies, many people believe that Microsoft should and could place a bid for them any day now.
These companies have some things in common when it comes to Microsoft. They all have collaborated closely with Microsoft on numerous occasions. They are on Microsoft Windows Server and have joined Microsoft in the cloud. They ensure that their products and services interop with Microsoft’s offering as best as possible.

These companies also compete fiercely in one or more sectors. Despite being close allies, they treat Microsoft as an enemy on the battlefield of enterprise software and services.
<h4>Citrix</h4>
Microsoft’s and Citrix’s main point of competition is in the field of Desktop Virtualization (DV). DV allows users to assess a desktop and its applications from a remote PC. One form of DV is Virtual Desktop Infrastructure. This where a user is served a remote PC, which has its own operating system. They compete in VDI through Microsoft’s Hyper-V and Citrix XenDesktop.

Microsoft and Citrix compete in Remote Desktop Virtualization, another form of DV. They compete in this field through Microsoft Remote Desktop Services and Citrix XenApp. XenApp is based on Remote Desktop Services; however, Citrix is becoming less dependent on it over time. The companies also compete in Enterprise Mobility Management.

Despite Microsoft competing with Citrix’s main products, Citrix has not been afraid to collaborate with the bigger of the technology companies. Their latest partnership was in 2017. According to the press release, “Microsoft and Citrix have partnered for over 25 years to ensure their products are best-in-class. The impact of the partnership is undeniable with Microsoft and Citrix having 230,000 joint customers and tens of millions of users that rely on a joint solution every day.”

The press release stated that through their powerful relationship business organization would receive:
<ul>
 	<li>Best-in-class security, scalability, management, and performance of enterprise software and online services.</li>
 	<li>Commitment to industry standards, organizational compliance, and new cloud computing trends.</li>
 	<li>Deep integration with Microsoft server and desktop operating systems and management tools.</li>
 	<li>A shared vision for flexible, seamless and powerful computing for today’s mobile workforce.</li>
</ul>
Straight from the horse’s mouth, Citrix and Microsoft are tightly integrated. If Microsoft wanted to buy them, not much resistance would be put up. Citrix has a market capitalization of 13 billion dollars. It has over 3 billion dollars in annual earnings and 400 million dollars in profits. This makes Citrix a very cheap purchase. The question has always been not if Microsoft will buy Citrix, but rather why has it not done so yet.
<h4>SAP SE</h4>
SAP SE is a German company that specializes in Enterprise Resource Planning. They compete with Microsoft’s Dynamics, which will become Dynamics 365 over the coming years. They also compete in databases through Microsoft SQL and SAP HAHA. They also have rival products in CRM, Human Resources, and Internet of Things (IoT).

However, they have a great relationship. They have had many partnerships. In their latest partnership in 2016, they announced the support for the SAP HANA platform deployment on Microsoft Azure. This provided new integrations between Microsoft Office 365 and cloud solutions from SAP. The partnership also provided enhanced management and security for custom SAP Fiori apps.
Three areas of focus for the partnership were:
<ul>
 	<li>New Deployment Option: SAP HANA on the Microsoft Azure cloud.</li>
 	<li>Cloud Services Integrations: Public Cloud Solutions from SAP and Office 365.</li>
 	<li>Flexibility in the Cloud: Management and Security of Custom SAP Fiori Apps.</li>
</ul>
SAP has a market capitalization of 138 billion dollars. They have annual revenue of 25 billion dollars and net income of 4.3 billion dollars. It is doing great and has started a successful transition to the could. 138 billion dollars minus premium is a lot of money and getting regulatory approval from the European Commission would be difficult. It would be the biggest technology acquisition ever. It would take many figureheads to agree that this purchase is wanted and needed. Yet, not many people would be surprised by it.
<h4>Cisco</h4>
Cisco is an enterprise company that specializes in both hardware and software. They provide networking, data center, internet security, and unified communications hardware and software. Their main point of competition with Microsoft is through unified communications and video conferencing. Their Cisco Spark competes with Skype For Business and Microsoft Team.

Cisco and Microsoft are very close. They have collaborated numerous times. From Skype For Business being integrated into Cisco Meetings to Office 365 in Cisco Sparks. According to a May 2017 blog post titled “Microsoft Collaborate to Power Intelligent Actions Exactly Where and When It’s Needed”, Cisco stated “Cisco and Microsoft already have a long history of collaboration in many areas, including IoT. The Cisco Jasper connectivity management platform has long been integrated into the Azure IoT Hub. In March, we partnered in the launch of the Microsoft IoT &amp; AI Insider Labs. And earlier this year we announced the Cisco Integrated System for Microsoft Azure Stack, ideal for those who want the full benefits of the Azure cloud in an on-premise environment.”

Cisco is worth 180 billion dollars. It has annual revenue of 48 billion dollars and net income of 9.6 billion dollars. This would be a massive deal if were ever to happen. Cisco comes with many hardware products and Microsoft would have to be committed to that part of the business if a purchase were ever to be made. Given how Microsoft mismanaged the Nokia acquisition, many would be rightly skeptical of Microsoft’s ability to successfully run a hardware business of Cisco’s size.

Microsoft does have experience with successful hardware through Xbox and the Surface Family. However, Xbox and Surface are not on the same scale as Cisco’s hardware business. If Microsoft could overcome their aversion to massive hardware undertaking, then they could buy Cisco with enough willpower. Honestly, if that were to happen, who would be surprised?
<h3>Shake Up The Tech World</h3>
If Microsoft were to manage to get any these, the tech world would never be the same again. These are likely to never happen, but it is fascinating to wonder how things would play out if they were to happen.
<h4>Salesforce.com</h4>
Saleforce.com is one of the biggest SaaS companies in the world, with a market cap of 78 billion dollars. They specialize in CRM. They are by far the biggest player in this sector. Microsoft has its own CRM product in the form of Dynamics CRM Online, which can be subscribed to as a single entity or as a part of Dynamics 365. There is scant updated information on the market share of the CRM market, but Microsoft is nowhere close to Salesforce. The impact of Dynamics 365 on the CRM market has not been assessed. Whatever, the current market share, Microsoft buying Salesforce, would make Microsoft many times stronger in the CRM sector.

This is not very likely to happen. There are many reasons for this, but the main reason is the relationship between Salesforce.com and Microsoft. In 2015 Microsoft tried to buy Salesforce.com for a reported 55 billion dollars, however, Salesforce.com wanted 70 billion dollars. Microsoft and Salesforce.com have also been enemies, however, at the time when the offer was made, they were starting to become friends. Yet, as the talks fell through, they renewed their fierce rivalry. Things got farther heated when Microsoft beat Salesforce.com to LinkedIn in 2016.
<h4>Amazon Web Service (AWS)</h4>
AWS is the runaway leader in the IaaS with an estimated market share of 33% and quarterly revenues of 4.58 billion dollars and 1.17 billion dollars in operating income. Many companies run on AWS including Netflix, Spotify, and Workday. Most importantly, Amazon.com runs on AWS. Therefore, even if a deal were to be made between Amazon and Microsoft, the logistics would be almost impossible. And why would Amazon want to sell when AWS is the clear leader in one of the twins that are the future of enterprise software. The twins are IAAS and SAAS. Farther more, AWS is the only profitable part of its business.
<h4>G Suite/Google Cloud</h4>
This one is near impossible, if not purely for the fact that Google and Microsoft are declared enemies. Google Cloud is the foundation of 90% of Alphabet’s businesses. It is impossible for Google Cloud to be ripped from online properties like Google.com and Gmail.com. There is one way that they could join. It could happen through both companies performing a spin-off. If there were ever to come a time when Microsoft wants to exist all consumer-facing products and services and Google wants to get out of the enterprise games, then this merger could happen.
Google makes 90% of its revenue from advertising, which is a direct to consumer offering. Despite all Google’s talk of the Enterprise, they barely make any money in that sector when compared to the other players. Microsoft, on the other hand, makes billions of dollars selling directly or indirectly to consumers. However, these are expensive dollars when compared to its very high margin enterprise business.

It possible to see a scenario where Google decides that it does not want to battle in Enterprise against Microsoft, Amazon, and Salesforce who each have 5 billion dollars in cloud revenue per quarter. Nadella is an enterprise guy. I am sure if he were given the upside Google Cloud/G Suite versus the current downside of Windows, he would choose Google Cloud/G Suite. Microsoft would be unstoppable in the collaboration and productivity technology sector. It would not be far behind Amazon in IaaS given Google’s good name with small businesses and the Open Source community. Combine that with Microsoft’s enterprise strength, Google Cloud and Azure would be unstoppable.

Google owns the biggest consumer Operating System in the world in Android, however, Microsoft owns the biggest desktop platform. Mobile might be the future, but the desktop is still king when it comes to cost per click, Google’s most precious performance metrics. If Google owned Windows, it could better serve advertisements to its consumers. It could carry the Google PlayStore to Windows. It could, for example, offer free to play triple AAA games, but place a massive banger advertisement or play a 15 seconds advertisement before the start of each gaming session. It would not have to worry about advertising inventory, it has the largest ever created. Google would also get several billion dollars in profitable revenue from Microsoft’s More Personal Computing business unit.

There would have to be some agreement between Google and Microsoft. Likely Google would retain the right to continue using the Google Cloud for its online services. Google would have to need to start diverting to its private cloud from Microsoft’s new cloud over time. Google could also agree to continue to buy more cloud from Microsoft. Microsoft would have to split Windows Enterprise from Windows Pro and Home.

This seems far-stretch, but not impossible. At the end of the day, Google is an advertising company, you simply cannot advertise to the enterprise. Windows would provide over 500 million users on a modern operating system that is built for advertising with its start screen. Microsoft is an enterprise company that rather would talk to people in the C-Suite than the “sheep” Apple command.
<h4>Oracle</h4>
Oracle and Microsoft are not friends and they have never been. This is an official designation. Oracle has for long been a Microsoft Worldwide Partner Conference (WPC) Enemies List. This is a list that prohibits employers from attending Microsoft’s WPC. The list included employees from Google, Oracle, Salesforce.com, and VMware. Oracle was removed from the list in 2014 and replaced by Amazon.

They had strike a deal to put Oracle software on Azure in 2013. This was the likely reason they were removed from the WPC Enemy List. However, this was done out of necessity. Oracle products, especially its database, are very popular. Azure was a growing star in the field of IaaS at the time, their enterprise customers demanded that they work together in the cloud. They wanted to use NoSQL on Azure.
This acquisition would not happen for the same reason that would prevent an IBM merger, the price, and necessity.
<h4>International Business Machine (IBM)</h4>
This one would be easy if both companies wanted it. They are not the greatest of enemies nor the greatest of friends. Their businesses are very compatible. Their sales teams like contacts in virtually all Enterprise in the world.

The biggest obstacle in the way of any possible deal would be the price. IBM has a market cap of 137 billion dollars. Microsoft has 136.932 billion dollars in cash. Microsoft always buys in cash, therefore, to buy IBM, Microsoft would need to borrow several billion dollars. Given that both companies are still very profitable, this acquisition is unlikely to happen because of a lack of need.
<h3>Others</h3>
These are just random companies that Microsoft could acquire that does not quite fit into the other categories. They can also be companies that go beyond what Satya Nadella has purchased while being the CEO of Microsoft.
<h4>Inuit</h4>
Inuit is a financial software company that develops and sells financial, accounting and tax preparation software and related services for small businesses, accountants, and individuals. This is not Microsoft area of expertise. However, with a market capitalization of 39 billion dollars and revenues of 5.2 billion dollars that generated 1 billion dollars in profit, maybe Microsoft should break the bank. They could even use QuickBooks to do the accounting.
<h4>Adobe</h4>
Adobe’s most popular products built for designers are not Microsoft’s cup of tea. However, it has many products just for the enterprise consumers. They have some great cloud enterprise services like Experience Cloud, Marketing Cloud, Advertising Cloud and Campaign. All these would fit well into Microsoft’s profile, especially with Bing.com.

Adobe made 5.9 billion dollars last year with a profit of 1 billion dollars. It is valued at 90 billion dollars, which makes it very expensive. It does have unlimited upside, given that it has successfully transformed itself into a cloud company. Every Adobe does is in the cloud. Microsoft is all about the cloud. Adobe might be expensive, but it is innovating as fast as a start-up in the cloud. If Microsoft were to burn a massive hole in its overseas cash stash, Adobe would be the company to do it on.
<h4>Cloudflare</h4>
Cloudflare started as a simple application to find the source of email spam. From there it grew into a service that protects websites from all manner of attacks, while simultaneously optimizing performance. Cloudflare services include content delivery network, DDoS mitigation, Internet security services and distributed domain name server services.

Cloudflare’s goal is to help build a better Internet. They say they are one of the highest trafficked entity on the Internet.
<ul>
 	<li>They serve more web traffic than Twitter, Amazon, Apple, Instagram, Bing, &amp; Wikipedia combined.</li>
 	<li>When they push code, it immediately affects over 200 million web surfers.</li>
 	<li>Every day, more than 10,000 new customers sign-up for Cloudflare service.</li>
 	<li>Every week, the average Internet user touches them more than 500 times.</li>
 	<li>They serve data from over 118 data centers around the world.</li>
</ul>
Cloudflare is a private company with a valuation of 3.2 billion dollars. It is said to be profitable. It runs on millions of sites on the web, making it a very valuable property. It would be a good fit for Microsoft Azure. After all, Microsoft uses security as one the unique value of Azure over Amazon Web Service.
<h4>Cloudera Inc</h4>
According to the About section on the Cloudera Inc website, Cloudera was founded in 2008 by former employees from some of Silicon Valley’s leading companies, including Christophe Biscigli from Google, Amr Awadallah from Yahoo, Mike Olson from Oracle and Jeff Hammerbacher from Facebook. They believed that open source, open standards, and open markets are best. Cloudera has more than 1,600 employees. They have offices in 24 countries around the globe. Their headquarters is in Palo Alto, California.

Cloudera provides Apache Hadoop-based software, support and services, and training to business customers. Cloudera's open-source Apache Hadoop distribution, CDH (Cloudera Distribution Including Apache Hadoop), targets enterprise-class deployments of that technology. Basically, it is a Big Data company.

It is not a profitable company. In its latest quarterly report, it reported revenue of 74 million dollars but had a loss of 66.6 million dollars. With a market cap of just 2 billion dollars, this could be a cheap way for Microsoft to get some technology and talent to add to the capacity it already has with Azure.
<h4>Docker Inc</h4>
According to Docker’s website, Docker is the only container platform provider to address every application across the hybrid cloud. Docker enables true independence between applications and infrastructure and developers and IT. This unlocks their potential and creates a model for better collaboration and innovation.

Docker comes in two versions; a free community edition and a paid enterprise edition. It has a valuation of 1 billion dollars. Microsoft can easily afford it. Microsoft already offers Docker on Azure, so it would be easy to integrate Docker into the Azure platform.

[maxbutton id="1" ]

[amazon_link asins='B01CUQ17SU,B071FMXF95,3839123038,B0041ORN6U,B00L0LIM62,1484229037,0609607995,B075VCXGVM' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='5360b775-da47-11e7-90e5-456f31600af5']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>7</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:52:27]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-05 14:52:27]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[who-should-microsoft-buy-next]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="acquisition"><![CDATA[Acquisition]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft"><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[8]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_22efc7629e364d13f81a2201335f55a5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_ac564d24f497bf0269fd11fa88b44b83]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_ac564d24f497bf0269fd11fa88b44b83]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512485552]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3b9ad6e4ecf4fcb8f1eddf1c7892a44b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_ab0cbaa2aa88ff73b97a1de45aea6f9f]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_fcf90d902d55a176d3dc67ad2474bc2e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4623b8dfef6cbb640d8c30363538ff59]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="gjmVYJSjdY"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=gjmVYJSjdY" data-secret="gjmVYJSjdY" width="525" height="296" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_4623b8dfef6cbb640d8c30363538ff59]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512485556]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6bcc49344a81daf4d45b837efd607da6]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_03b548ca6d6b651fde1f2059c54bd16a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0068d2de40292627829ce97166b2a096]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_34dc4d7988129891ec3b575d0363c9a2]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_7cc1e64faea1cb72cfa83a5e8475888a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4d5f00af7ee0c78f4f6c5218bdb2cc8a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1010420709b35879fea23aac9a08593b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8905c895e586aae6969998f3bb29ec6d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d33e6fff2ec2742ba723f8dcecf8ff3c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_fe3d47a8db66dbd6b2b2f1e1a4390046]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_aa2bc74386edd87fa68b2d53527c64a6]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_68d54024760fbd7219ec844404275f11]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_eb19d3659f91d4f2f476671a8e3f9194]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_eb19d3659f91d4f2f476671a8e3f9194]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512486045]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_98a41ab9ca111956038818cebfddea71]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c1ee9d2038c5e53d818fd3c3586785e7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6db2df4c95a4365d4e6377f9838507e6]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c54c88435ca7feec64c53590358930df]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="6l8Poi4lIO"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=6l8Poi4lIO" data-secret="6l8Poi4lIO" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_c54c88435ca7feec64c53590358930df]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512486048]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_7b808f2e02c5b54c767bf8b2af362b62]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c9ac2229bdf84078b1c89de0e8bfc893]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_748dcaa610a372469aa6a08f49f610d3]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_ac7b593618d69f3e4966cd0ed2cbf2c7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0ac59b0be41099f64f804bcf042e7d29]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4649dd2faf31f6aa27ea35028a29d902]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1890f6234c4790c3a463aa70993b169a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8fdf4ea7e54da8208c9dae195832c2c7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a739b5416d7cd015fb5f5262659b88ab]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6640c5c982b2d80f97b6d46004a91950]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0be1dfd0207f37faf767f5478fa4d56a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4919ddf6692a05d7bfcbd40cfab613fc]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_42cd0abb4346431355375ac53e483cf5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_42cd0abb4346431355375ac53e483cf5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512486913]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a2db3abefd879482a2b5316e61b6f9c7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2f8795cdfe1f2fa8f6e1a764200d304b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_45ece56f19cc91fea2031374ded0b55f]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_69e48edd14bc650fad88f83366981ddf]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="PDQN3HfYw9"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=PDQN3HfYw9" data-secret="PDQN3HfYw9" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_69e48edd14bc650fad88f83366981ddf]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512486917]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_985e555d7df88a86c4b1cc2c32f0132c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1dfa0d790d79122f76bba14dd519eb57]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e96216710a5e98feaebe5f898f49d80a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8cffb01b556b7058beb03e7ca367cc59]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1be5e0fcd48ddacff83f8d5e8ba30ffa]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_869dface49af0d14a5065ccb67877ec4]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c9c1ddb68ae256c008d807313a7a1f1a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8c02527f769897ff67031a1604f21cd6]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0728bd20f0a1e3af6ef57a49e87b6940]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e2dd4b0df9d2deaeb80106fe40fe4725]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0ac29bdb7d058cce3cb973eac78d795d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6330704321]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_27511679c0f2d6c8bc71f91d7531c398]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_096ea3a71dcfc37299a01e3b51aa667e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_096ea3a71dcfc37299a01e3b51aa667e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512487811]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f15c6e5de282c6f0cd98f8c0f53029fd]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_71dfd5bc5a42698f2504c980e17cf69e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_88d052f4981ac7175a5e830d8ba53add]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_76a19b6c44e86fb83843f1c77708fda1]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="A5aGcqo0iw"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=A5aGcqo0iw" data-secret="A5aGcqo0iw" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_76a19b6c44e86fb83843f1c77708fda1]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512487814]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9282ee4c8f3d9f768bcae147833549e9]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1ace1562556d15e77af8877dc72a8a56]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a67eb8e9c77de611014331f1e8730b37]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3d6216230a116f722e35b1c4608318d0]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e7081062fa444d0ae5f4b0936b3058c6]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c663598db1c9a78003695a2602e71069]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c568d4f2af7c8c8e68100192d45f1c13]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_28ebab0d0d093aacbb9df2e9c8f4c3c0]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1b5b6d2f118494551eabb0ef08607a0c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d882deee0bda5d4e00a0e04ff173cfb5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d59bde79e6d98551fe816e863b24dc75]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_page_template]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_19c533b6d9f1bd92f56b6ffba26c0621]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d2728f2d6e4f2419554e9ab326fbe186]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_d2728f2d6e4f2419554e9ab326fbe186]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512488596]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9dc536e5e0d0cfe5c8565752bc89767f]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_980e85fa0fabdcde7e5f28eda0123282]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_470a3c8de00db46a537e7cc125af4195]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_65d6e775b6bf998d0d26c71ee9925337]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="vDPII3IHyv"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=vDPII3IHyv" data-secret="vDPII3IHyv" width="474" height="267" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_65d6e775b6bf998d0d26c71ee9925337]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512488600]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_13329614f77a81375d19af2e4ba8c9fe]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5ce3e71013f72af71fd52c08bd1cd035]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9422b2a8b1563e3099e4230ecae7d4a4]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f40529010d9b83e2808de1d59adf7855]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_70beb11dcf75d430fbf5286285b9cab4]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2e1b71d063150904f1a68b2642a85266]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8d44df60a0d9000c0e24b02356e37d3d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2f8787a648382c466c2dcc6019eeb117]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9485e2a168e9583e6da56ebe21944d01]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f0dc48894c8e779d566144b341ecd842]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e158d8a1e4a370f6dab3f97f46663198]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_572a28a315da5484d9390d280fc1544b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4ec413d2275f7b1503c2cfc54134216e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_4ec413d2275f7b1503c2cfc54134216e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512488899]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a66d8f0925370f03f8470eed6b7156d1]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_986cb6e3c052c819cb50584c62994a39]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2b445c1d2d2d86b93a7f8f3c3dbd2eb7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2a0564118f588ba30cc46de0670391cf]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="otXWcJlka2"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=otXWcJlka2" data-secret="otXWcJlka2" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_2a0564118f588ba30cc46de0670391cf]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512488902]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c5ccd953b11968f4d06db4ea95acdcb5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2bce66a12186d78e261a2a8119938c3b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_23d1f6757f0453e40edfe9f5a704d4ab]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4b9f4f1320109c90071f526c152d0405]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_7ed2fcb8df66a88d0ae7c7f33ef277d8]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9f3db9096129b6aece7e8f23467dd710]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2aaaab2c0f865cdd4d9f5d41d0e0b53b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f0b7327e653a9a10ad0ab65c61d6b5bf]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a6e9d6ef886893c4693416bf73640f8e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_cb18a77a6f3e361ac8ed41f8e7be43cf]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_8aed868c6ef8873f3ac621649b574af8]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5ca0830fd5af0fe6ccc92933ec6a5836]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_298b630c763cb61eec90458177141369]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6121087b7c384095b7fdf04c7dce795b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_6121087b7c384095b7fdf04c7dce795b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512489025]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d96be2ddce3a8d727c6b343d4c47e792]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6213ffe33dee41c657fc92a77822fc0e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_ba21eabac767d50832ef5cf90031b646]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5326a425c7532c2b5b119f0044839129]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="8dFGX0m1Ut"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=8dFGX0m1Ut" data-secret="8dFGX0m1Ut" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_5326a425c7532c2b5b119f0044839129]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512489028]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_eee67327d490e30304d2bcd85b1ef62b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0e3f48b3904a61f337113eb416901aaf]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_297a2bcbac93a06051f93c9f4ceac18b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_d52d1941b320ccae68b6476ed4e9d939]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5ab60141fd2e0da8dd603ceaab15ae2d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c08b2b66a9b8ae67653cafdab0898f23]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0438674f0d5bd25c519f4015b3006be7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6a863d520df94461a9a206daab04880f]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_74b5fdea613ae6969c34c003699ffcce]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6d57798f37d6a041a43d847734fa7b0c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9cb9c4a6c7021ead46ff1e9bc6867333]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e49b32747657a0c0cbe1197007fe1322]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_b7900205e2244671dc9e57c421bc7f83]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_b7900205e2244671dc9e57c421bc7f83]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512489524]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6c5ebc0fc759b94300fc629126872689]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_dc53dec2e817fea8053291c728f78bff]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6dd556a252ffca237b607421e2fbf3e0]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_924086272facb1e84bb64a91de986ad7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="XaYDPKxVa8"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=XaYDPKxVa8" data-secret="XaYDPKxVa8" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_924086272facb1e84bb64a91de986ad7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512489527]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_152115cdb105449c989d95274463536d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_168afe6d5a764fd3b5a0a0f446140a9e]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f730f2e36adcfad78caf62c91b0f288d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_26244fe6965ce47b9a2e73c728185711]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_b7c4060b5c28442b2e8e07db975b6aed]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_4058e536ba2edcb11daeb1425c73e571]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9a469211193e1b1ab57b1182848aa807]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_48fbfff1f0567e1e631e32dfb5ee3ca2]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_20d2367efe815fe3f1432a048f0c462b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5d9d619db9bb695173f76d1488bac8b5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_524f78c23657df06cc3a29ef6baed591]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_dab9c14f465512f524162f2fee73cc0b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_dab9c14f465512f524162f2fee73cc0b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512490015]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e6a8033295d0fc4b0d11f108d95de8e8]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_19be477db734b5cd06c910c4bbc0a8ca]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6160c228091140e70e22a8e93ec199df]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a0e903b4a657357ebbb668ddbb59e9c1]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="u8gFkm8pqN"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=u8gFkm8pqN" data-secret="u8gFkm8pqN" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_a0e903b4a657357ebbb668ddbb59e9c1]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512490018]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0000aca14e00343095a3dec298322e7d]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_227c07912729a6c3a80ecd9749286b72]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a3f6b05034f55aee8b9e74cedb2f0b5a]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c5616a6c2778a82203c18c54f74147cd]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_b1fa69e9e846fb1aa1f7bc9ad89f8016]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_3d5d278d7f2335f8c924155996cbf4f7]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f1d46f3a0d019d000febba551c2daa41]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_b3ab0f1522b6e5771df9d17f2c79ec80]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_a6cff9ddaf91b34247860d82da884047]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_0253a851601e4bfdbb8c78da8b8fc9a6]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_60eb08cb16ef18fbd82547c8b4fa5b2b]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_f19cbee50db7d9e41078897e6cb53814]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_6fd9d1028a4e8caaa3a3efee808d8258]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<a href="https://techcrunch.com/2017/07/28/aws-wont-be-ceding-its-massive-market-share-lead-anytime-soon/">AWS won&#8217;t be ceding its massive market share lead anytime&nbsp;soon</a>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_6fd9d1028a4e8caaa3a3efee808d8258]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512491816]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2a57138e6c5b66022a0bbb4cb2d87f32]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_44d8be56770282dde6f159ae97ca28c0]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_c03903b36c480f356a4f42f6202e8045]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_5adbd4f56fec8a6f9cfef0ed5c5c7425]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[<blockquote class="wp-embedded-content" data-secret="GzcZFxJ85g"><a href="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/">SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud</a></blockquote><iframe class="wp-embedded-content" sandbox="allow-scripts" security="restricted" style="position: absolute; clip: rect(1px, 1px, 1px, 1px);" src="https://news.microsoft.com/2016/05/17/sap-and-microsoft-usher-in-new-era-of-partnership-to-accelerate-digital-transformation-in-the-cloud/embed/#?secret=GzcZFxJ85g" data-secret="GzcZFxJ85g" width="600" height="338" title="&#8220;SAP and Microsoft usher in new era of partnership to accelerate digital transformation in the cloud&#8221; &#8212; Stories" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe>]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_time_5adbd4f56fec8a6f9cfef0ed5c5c7425]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512491824]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_7fd6368595803a0347e2f297e5d30af3]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_e34fc3a7903cb690b9ee59bad0c5b465]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_1fbfbe7c88d34779196e84d1f746a2b5]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_ceb7563b61bee9e9cd78d0e0f31fdb1c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_399b2edb0ebccf50fe74a016addee493]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_53904d6aeaa17ad6e7a0e87d5c0ef051]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_432e4518f8f80d28c0b3487b082095c3]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_efcd47145cdd3f495c89bf3ece8ac175]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_82ffb7b7950def692257a4c05a89279c]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_9f595deef8b401647241d1cf746737ef]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_oembed_2c47bd9a3ca9c1d5d8ad9fa27fb65b29]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[flash_page_layout]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default-layout]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[30]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Microsoft Surface: From Rags to Riches</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/microsoft-surface-from-rags-to-riches/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 06:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3><a href="http://amzn.to/2yOkPVh" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Surface</a>:  Rags</h3>
The Microsoft Surface Book 2 is on the horizon, to be released on November 17, 2017. That is a statement many tech watchers thought could ever be made. The Surface family is big now. It is successful too and if all is to go according to plan, an ultra-mobile Surface should add to that Success.

This is a far cry from the 900 million dollars writedown that the original Surface, the Surface RT, had to endure. This lost was in part due to Microsoft’s hubris; it believed it could sell six million Surface RTs at launch. At that time, the calls for the discontinuation of the Surface line were very loud. They were not making money but losing it. They were competing with other PC manufacturers, which could have affected a large portion of Microsoft’s revenue.

The operating system these RT devices were based on was confusing to users. It had a desktop, however, it could not run x86 applications. At the time, Microsoft was not a force in the mobile sector. Therefore, its Windows store did not have enough apps to entice consumers who are used to an almost unlimited number of applications in mobile stores.
<h3><a href="http://amzn.to/2yOkPVh" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Surface</a>: Riches</h3>
Those are the bad old days now. Microsoft has learned from its past mistakes. It does not make too many Surface units and the Surface line is indeed profitable. All of the Surfaces available comes with the full version of Windows, besides the Surface Hub. Each new Surface brand is innovative or ultra-premium. Microsoft no longer makes me-too devices. If a Surface is not special, it will not see the light of day.

This was the case with the Surface Mini that was never released, despite 15,000 units being manufactured for testing and demonstration. It was canned before releasing due to not having any outstanding features.

The Surface devices are hero products that show what Windows is capable of. Before the Surface line, PC makers were only making tradition and boring clamshell laptops. Now OEMs like Dell, HP and Acer are making innovative and premium devices that often goes beyond a clamshell and into realms like 360 degrees conversion and 4k touch screen.

These premium PCs sits perfectly alongside the members of the Surface family such as:
<h4 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2zKXRlb" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Surface Pro</a></h4>
<a href="http://amzn.to/2zKXRlb"><img width="300" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-111 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/surface-pro-300x300.jpg" /></a>A hybrid laptop/tablet that has a detachable keyboard whose standout feature is its 180-degrees kickstand.
<h4 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2hH3Kcx" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Surface Book 2</a></h4>
<a href="http://amzn.to/2hH3Kcx"> <img width="300" height="300" class="size-medium wp-image-153 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/SURFACE-BOOK-2-300x300.jpg" /></a>This is the ultimate laptop. A powerful machine that can play the latest videos games at high resolution and frame rates. It also has a detachable screen leading to a portable experience after a gaming session or rendering a 4k scene in After Effects.
<h4 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2yRTm5f" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Surface Laptop</a></h4>
<a href="http://amzn.to/2yRTm5f"><img width="300" height="182" class="size-medium wp-image-112 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Surface-Laptop-300x182.jpg" /></a>

This is tradition laptop that is thought by many to be the best Windows laptop on the market.
<h4 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2zKVI98" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Surface Studio</a></h4>
<a href="http://amzn.to/2zKVI98"><img width="300" height="241" class="size-medium wp-image-154 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/surface-studio-300x241.jpg" /></a>

An all-in-one desktop PC that comes with an adjustable screen and powerful internal specifications.
<h4 style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/surface/devices/surface-hub/overview" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Surface Hub</a></h4>
<img width="1" height="1" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-12 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/p.gif" /><a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/surface/devices/surface-hub/overview"><img width="298" height="187" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-155 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Surface-Hub.jpg" /></a>

This a smartboard with its own computer, making a self-sustaining unit. It comes in 55 and 84 inches and Windows 10.
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2yPa2u0" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The Surface Mouse</a></p>
<a href="http://amzn.to/2yPa2u0"><img width="202" height="190" class="alignnone wp-image-156 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Surface-Mouse-300x283.jpg" /></a>A beautiful mouse made by one of the best mouse manufacturers in the world.
<h4 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2hEblsr" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Surface Pen</a></h4>
<a href="http://amzn.to/2hEblsr"><img width="149" height="149" class="alignnone wp-image-157 aligncenter" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/Surface-Pen-300x300.jpg" /></a>The pen that helped kick off the renaissance of the pen as a means of computer interaction.
<h3 style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://amzn.to/2yOkPVh" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Microsoft Surface</a>: The Future</h3>
<p style="text-align: left;">The Surface line started as a tabletop computer and in the near future, it could reach a 6 inches form factor. The transformation of the Surface line has been something to behold and I cannot wait for the future. I just want to see what Panos Panay, head of Microsoft hardware, and his team have in store for us next.</p>
[amazon_link asins='B01MD0JZHQ,B0163GNS5S,B01606KJ6C,B071SF41Y9,B076J5Y9Y1,B076J91H91,B076J15LKM,B0163GS05Q' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='94ae78b4-da45-11e7-9c69-9d5317bd8f87']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>24</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-11-17 06:13:00]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-11-17 06:13:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[microsoft-surface-from-rags-to-riches]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft-hardware"><![CDATA[Hardware]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft"><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft-surface"><![CDATA[Surface]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="surface"><![CDATA[surface]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="surface-phone"><![CDATA[Surface Phone]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_blog]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[deepdive-microsoft.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_author]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Revi Bennett]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_permalink]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2017/11/microsoft-surface-from-rags-to-riches.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_internal]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/feeds/7750722740907606385/posts/default/1830660811576394264]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6330752341]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[108]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[flash_page_layout]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default-layout]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[90]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Microsoft’s Failed Acquisitions</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/microsofts-failed-acquisitions/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Microsoft: A Company That Likes To Buy</h3>
Microsoft has been successful in many of its acquisition throughout its history. Some of the successful ones are Mojang-Minecraft, Skype Technologies, Visio Cooperation, Forethought Inc.-PowerPoint, RenderMorphics-Direct3D, Grove Networks-OneDrive, and Perceptive Pixel-Surface Hub.

Despite a long list of fruitful purchases, Microsoft is more known for its failure to capitalize on its new toys. I have listed Skype Technologies as a success story. Many people actively disagree with that notion. <a href="http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/12/is-skype-a-failure/">However, I argue that Skype has not been a failure</a>. Acquisitions, like Skype, can be argued about for a long time as to whether they have been successful or not.

That is not true for all of Microsoft’s purchase of other companies; there is no doubt about these acquisitions being busts. Two of Microsoft’s biggest busts are two of its biggest purchases. The companies involved these ill-fated mergers are aQuantive and Nokia.

Let us first look at aQuantive. It was bought by Microsoft on May 18, 2007, for $6 billion dollars. AQuantive was an advertising company that specialized in digital marketing. Its products and platforms included Atlas Solutions, DRIVE Performance Solutions, and Avenue A/Razorfish. At the time of the purchase, aQuantive was one of the biggest advertising agencies in the world. AQuantive was Microsoft’s biggest acquisition when it was bought. In 2012, however, it became Microsoft’s second-biggest writedown.
<h3>aQuantive: No Ads Placed</h3>
AQuantive was bought to make Microsoft a competitor in the online advertising space; to compete with the online giant that is Google. However, Microsoft was too late to the new era of online internet service. By 2012, five years after aQuantive became a part of the Microsoft family, Microsoft’s online business was still not profitable, including Bing.com. In fact, Bing only became profitable in the past two years.

While Bing has started to make money, Microsoft’s other online businesses were not so successful. In 2014, Microsoft stopped placing original articles on MSN.com and started serving third-party ads instead of its own advertisements. That has left the profitable Bing as Microsoft’s only fully-controlled online service.

AQuantive was a failure because Microsoft bought it as part of an ambitious project, yet showed little of the ambition and commitment that that project needed to succeed. This is not the last time that will make this fatal mistake.
<h3>Nokia: A Failure to Launch</h3>
In what has become Microsoft’s most ill-advised acquisition, on April 25, 2014, Microsoft completed the purchase of Nokia’s phone business for $7.2 billion dollars. Everybody knows who Nokia is, the fabled mobile phone manufacturer who has fallen rapidly from grace.

When Microsoft garbled-up Nokia smartphone division, Nokia was only shipping 5 million phones per quarter. At that time over 200 million smartphones were being shipped per quarter. Moreover, Nokia was not profitable, and it had not been for a long time. Nokia was the major manufacturer of Windows Phones with 90% market share. From that point of view, Microsoft had no real choice but to buy Nokia, given that Nokia had started making Android phones.

Making a bad purchase based on circumstances out of your control is still a bad purchase. However, it is nothing compared to doing everything to sabotage the Nokia deal. That is exactly what Microsoft and specifically Satay Nadella did. Nadella was against the Nokia from the very beginning.

It all started with the cancellation of the “Lumia 1030”, the most legendary Lumia that was never released. This was quickly followed by the underwhelming Lumia 940 and 940XL, released in 2015, that failed to create any excitement amongst the loyal Windows Phone fanbase. The two “flagship” Lumias were released with Windows 10 Mobile, which many Windows fans agree was worse than Windows 8.1.

Almost the entire value of Nokia was written off by Microsoft on July 28, 2015, with $7.2 billion dollars being written off and 7, 800 jobs being cut.
<h3>Windows Phone: It Is Dead!!!</h3>
Windows 10 Mobile has not been given much love by Microsoft. When it was placed permanently on Redstone 2 Feature 2 maintenance branch, fans began to worry that the death of Windows phones was at hand. When Microsoft decided to remove itself from the mobile phone market and retrench, the picture was clearly on the walls; Windows Phone was dead.

The final nail was tightly placed in the coffin when Microsoft Executive Joe Belfiore went on Twitter to say that Windows Phone would only be getting security updates and other patches going forward. He also stated that no new hardware would be made using Windows 10 Mobile.

This is another case of Microsoft buying a company to be a part of a grand and ambitious project and then decided not to match those great ideas with effective and precise execution.
<h3>Microsoft: Its All About the Profits</h3>
Microsoft has always been an ambitious company, no one can deny that. However, its ambitions are not always given the runway they need, especially under the leadership of Satya Nadella. Microsoft makes a lot of profit and any endeavour they peruse that does not show a path to profitable will be cut. That was the fate of aQuantive and Nokia. They were not showing signs of profitability nor were unique in the market. With them, Microsoft was gaining neither market share nor mindshare; this made them killable and thus they were killed.

[amazon_link asins='B071VZKDDP,B075FLG6MV,B072FN59FH,B075MC8D1T,B01606IDL0,B017V4OEYA,B017V4OHIS,B012CKVZ18' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='61c9727a-da45-11e7-85bb-a32071bc5ade']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>25</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-11-14 06:03:00]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-11-14 06:03:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[microsofts-failed-acquisitions]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="aquantive"><![CDATA[aQuantive]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft-hardware"><![CDATA[Hardware]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="merger"><![CDATA[Merger]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft"><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="nokia"><![CDATA[nokia]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="skype"><![CDATA[skype]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_blog]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[deepdive-microsoft.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_author]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Revi Bennett]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_permalink]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2017/11/microsofts-failed-acquisitions_13.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_internal]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/feeds/7750722740907606385/posts/default/5921866229268010082]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6330751431]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[67]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[flash_page_layout]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default-layout]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[60]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[7]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yst_is_cornerstone]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_focuskw_text_input]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_focuskw]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_linkdex]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[73]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Bing Makes New Experience Easier this Holiday</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/bing-makes-new-experience-easier-this-holiday__trashed/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<strong>The Christmas holidays is one of the most wondrous times of the year. This is the time of the year when seemingly long-lost friends and family are close to you again. With limit but valuable time with them, you will want to ensure that are shown a good time. Lightning does strike in the same place twice, so you will need to show them a new experience to gain the most from the holidays. </strong><strong>New experiences can be hard to find; luckily for you, Bing is here to help. If you want to eat, shop or just hang out, Bing can help you get there.</strong><br/><br/><strong>If you have heard of a place to eat, but you know nothing about it besides its name, Bing can assist you. You can simply search for the restaurant’s phone number. With the phone number, you can get all the information about the restaurant you will drag your brother to. This is one time of the year that he must stop playing games and be entertained with his family.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Your brother reluctantly decides to go with you to the restaurant, but before you can leave, you realize you have forgotten the direction and distance to the restaurant. Bing knows that information, and it will tell you where the restaurant is and the distance of the best route you should take.</strong><br/><br/><strong>You are driving to the restaurant, and your high school friend calls and says she might be a little late. You ask her what time she will arrive; she says no earlier than 10:00 pm. You are not sure what time the restaurant will close, so let your brother search for the opening hours of the restaurant. He tells you that it closes at 12:00 pm on Fridays. You are happy as you tell your friend that she will be just on time.</strong><br/><br/><strong>Therefore, this holiday, the one thing you should not worry about is a new place to have new experiences with your friends and family.</strong>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>26</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-11-13 11:45:00]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-11-13 11:45:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bing-makes-new-experience-easier-this-holiday__trashed]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[trash]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="bing"><![CDATA[bing]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft"><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="search"><![CDATA[search]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_blog]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[deepdive-microsoft.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_author]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Revi Bennett]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_permalink]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2017/11/bing-makes-new-experience-easier-this.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_internal]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/feeds/7750722740907606385/posts/default/3886599878741559407]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6330751230]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_status]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_time]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512495403]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_desired_post_slug]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bing-makes-new-experience-easier-this-holiday]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Is Skype A Failure</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/is-skype-a-failure/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 05:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>One Billion Downloads</h3>
Recently Microsoft announced that Skype has been downloaded 1 billion times from the Google Play Store. This should be a time of celebration in the Microsoft tech community; however, the moment was met with little enthusiasm. Only Google apps, which are downloaded to every Play Store Android, and Facebook’s full app, Messenger and Whatsapp can boost of this milestone. Despite the massive download total, Skype only has 300 million monthly active users (MAU).

Two of the above-mentioned apps; Whatsapp, Messenger and other such as iMessage/FaceTime, LINE has ensured that Skype is longer the dominant communication it was five to ten years ago. Skype has not only been slowed by competition, but also by the numerous bugs that have plagued the platform in recent years; from notifications not syncing to calls being duplicated.
<h3>No Longer The Leader</h3>
However, if one were to determine the success of Skype, we must first decide what Microsoft bought Skype for. A casual observer would insist that Skype was brought as a consumer play, to be the continued leader in consumer communication. Skype is nowhere close to being the leader in consumer communication. Skype’s 300 MAUs hardly compares to Whatsapp’s 1.2 billion MAUs and Whatsapp’s parent company’s Messenger, 1.2 billion MAUs. By those metrics, Skype has been a failure, given the head start it had over the platforms that are ahead of it now.
<h3>Is Skype A Failure?</h3>
It is easy to thus declare Skype a failure, but to proceed like that, we must take into account that Microsoft is an enterprise company who does consumer tech on the side. Microsoft competes in the field of Unified Communications (This is a system that unifies all the communications needs of a company such as voice chat, instant message, screen/desktop sharing and teleconference etc.). Microsoft started out with Office Communicator in 2007. Office Communicator was then changed to Lync in 2011. In 2014 Lync was then renamed to Skype of Business.

Microsoft bought Skype for 8.5 billion dollars in 2011 at the time when Lync was establishing itself as a player in the Unified Communication field. Microsoft saw Skype as a possible competitor to its baby Lync. At the time eBay was a willing seller, so in Microsoft’s eyes it could do nothing but buy Skype. It could not afford for Apple or Google to get their hands on it.

Letting it go was risking letting go of the thoughts of being a leader in Unified Communication. That much was clear in Microsoft’s 10-K filings where they assigned a value of 9.8 billion dollars to Skype. Of that 9.8 billion, 9 billion was Enterprise value while the remaining 800 million dollars were consumer value.
<h3>Skype Has Served Its Purpose</h3>
Lync has been successfully rebranded as Skype for Business. The Skype team created Microsoft Teams (A rival to Slack, which is valued at 8 billion) and Microsoft Teams has been so successful in its rollout that Microsoft will move Skype for Business users to that platform in the near to midterm future. Microsoft had planned to buy Slack for 8 billion, but Microsoft had so much fate in the Skype team to build something better, decided against that.

Given Slack value and the success of Teams so far, the Skype team has saved Microsoft several billion dollars. If one were to look at what Skype has done for Microsoft in the Enterprise in the six years Microsoft owned it, Skype has been a massive success.

[amazon_link asins='B008M721MS,B0035G87MY,B002HXW984,B01BBKZ520,B006DYM3RA,B0772L495M,B00CRJWW2G,B0080CE5M4' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='1f94e6f2-da45-11e7-a1a2-0d98f67d6606']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>27</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-11-12 05:29:00]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-11-12 05:29:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[is-skype-a-failure]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="communication"><![CDATA[Communication]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="messaging"><![CDATA[messaging]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft"><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="skype"><![CDATA[skype]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="whatsapp"><![CDATA[whatsapp]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_blog]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[deepdive-microsoft.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_author]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Revi Bennett]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_permalink]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2017/11/is-skype-failure_11.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_internal]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/feeds/7750722740907606385/posts/default/8596629670275267585]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6330753317]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[122]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[flash_page_layout]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default-layout]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[30]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Failed Acquisitions]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email><![CDATA[noreply@blogger.com]]></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url>http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/14/microsofts-failed-acquisition/</wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP><![CDATA[127.0.0.1]]></wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date><![CDATA[2017-11-19 02:12:28]]></wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-11-19 02:12:28]]></wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[[…] have listed Skype Technologies as a success story. Many people actively disagree with that notion. However, I argue that Skype has not been a failure. Acquisitions, like Skype, can be argued about for a long time as to whether they have been […]]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved><![CDATA[1]]></wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>0</wp:comment_user_id>
			<wp:commentmeta>
				<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_internal]]></wp:meta_key>
				<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/feeds/7750722740907606385/8596629670275267585/comments/default/4197744639786315774]]></wp:meta_value>
			</wp:commentmeta>
		</wp:comment>
		<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>6</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Failed Acquisitions &#8211; Microsoft World]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url>http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/14/microsofts-failed-acquisitions/</wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP><![CDATA[185.27.134.228]]></wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date><![CDATA[2017-12-05 17:35:13]]></wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-05 17:35:13]]></wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[[&#8230;] have listed Skype Technologies as a success story. Many people actively disagree with that notion. However, I argue that Skype has not been a failure. Acquisitions, like Skype, can be argued about for a long time as to whether they have been [&#8230;]]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved><![CDATA[1]]></wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type><![CDATA[pingback]]></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>0</wp:comment_user_id>
		</wp:comment>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Success of the “Surface Phone”</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/11/the-success-of-the-surface-phone/</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 05:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Microsoft: The Enterprise Company</h3>
I have not been the biggest fan of Satya Nadella when it comes to the fullness of Microsoft's efforts in mobile. However, I have always been a Microsoft fan more than I am a windows fan. Sure, I would love for Windows Phone to be on fifty million phones per quarter and one million apps to be in the Microsoft Store. Yet, looking back at the past, Microsoft’s cloud revenue being at 5 billion dollars per quarter is far more important.

It is easy to look at International Business Machine (IBM) and say that will be Microsoft’s fate. It is true that no one is excited about IBM, but for their stockholders. What is also true is that IBM still makes a boatload of money; 19.2 billion in revenue in their last quarterly report. Therefore, even if Microsoft becomes IBM, it will still make a lot of money.
<h3>Will A Lack of Consumer Focus Hurt?</h3>
People will say that the lack of a consumer present will leave the way open for Apple and Google to take the Enterprise. The recent example of Delta and General Electronics (GE)abandoning Microsoft seems to solidify that notion. However, a quick look at Microsoft’s recent quarterly report shows that Windows Commercial Products revenue grew by 7%. This is the Windows that is sold to the largest cooperate organizations in the world through Windows Volume Licensing. Your IT manager does care about what you are using, only what he thinks will make the users most productive. Windows is still the most Enterprise ready OS in the world and by a wide margin.

Oracle, Amazon Web Service, Salesforce.com, VMware, SAP, these are some of the biggest Enterprise Tech companies. None of these has successful consumer platform. Some might say Amazon.com has a successful consumer business, but AWS has very little to do with Amazon.com; no developer would use AWS because they love Amazon.com. Microsoft is an enterprise company and Nadella is an enterprise guy, through and through. He has driven the growth of Microsoft enterprise offering tremendously since taking over.

The lack of a real mobile presence since 2015 has not stopped that. Microsoft has spent 26 billion dollars on LinkedIn, which provides 1 billion dollars in revenue and about 100 million dollars in profits after amortization and other expenses related to the acquisition, per quarter. This should be proof of the lengths Microsoft will go to remain dominant in enterprise software, their bread and butter.
<h3>The Money Is In the Enterprise</h3>
Enterprise is boring, but it also makes a lot of money and that revenue is highly profitable. The consumer side of tech is exciting, but only Apple, Samsung, Google, Facebook, Amazon, eBay and Microsoft without phones make a profit from catering to consumers. Selling to consumers is not the easiest thing for a tech company to do. It is easy to see, at least from a for-profit business perspective, why Microsoft has gotten rid of Groove, Band, Windows Phone, Surface Mini etc.

Microsoft still has plays in the realm of consumer tech such as XBOX, Bing and to a certain extent the Surface line. All those have two things in common: they are profitable on their own as well having relatively high consumer mindshare. All these businesses had rough starts, but they were early enough or unique enough to justify the continued investment in Nadella’s eyes.
<h3>How The Surface Phone Will Succeed</h3>
If the Surface Phone is to be successful in the long run, it does not need to sell five million units per quarter, but it must show how it is going stand on its own. There is good news for the Surface Phone, the Surface line already stands on its own. If the Surface line continues to be successful, the Surface Phone will be ok.

The Surface Phone is not being made to be profitable, therefore, it has to be exciting to the niche it is targeting and that will guarantee that the Surface Phone will be exciting. I would be excited about the Surface Phone, even if you do not intend to buy it or you do not trust Microsoft anymore.

[amazon_link asins='B01606IDL0,B072J8RDZM,B076J184LM,B016C874Z2,B0163GNS5S,B07193J237,B0727VQK39,B0163GQJOU' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='a948a1ae-da44-11e7-aa60-fb79a38bb7cf']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>28</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-11-12 05:18:00]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-11-12 05:18:00]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-success-of-the-surface-phone]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft-hardware"><![CDATA[Hardware]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="image"><![CDATA[Image]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft"><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="surface"><![CDATA[surface]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="surface-phone"><![CDATA[Surface Phone]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_blog]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[deepdive-microsoft.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_author]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Revi Bennett]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_permalink]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2017/11/the-success-of-surface-phone_11.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[blogger_internal]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/feeds/7750722740907606385/posts/default/262209285989689134]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[125]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[flash_page_layout]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default-layout]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6331086953]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[90]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/12/171__trashed/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 05:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msftworld.ml/?p=171</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[TESTING

&nbsp;

[amazon_link asins='B06Y4GZS9C,B0762S8PYM,B0746NCNSG,B01LD4MGY4,B0176WQ792,B073YHNPC6,B07527JC71' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='1ae9ca19-da44-11e7-98cc-67e4e5a3ca90']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>171</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-12-06 05:14:15]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-06 05:14:15]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[171__trashed]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[trash]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6331985780]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_status]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[90]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_trash_meta_time]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1512537312]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_desired_post_slug]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[171]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Software As A Service (SaaS)</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/12/software-as-a-service-saas/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msftworld.ml/?p=231</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Software As A Service (SaaS)</h2>
Software as a Service (SaaS) is one of the most important types of software/service that an enterprise technology can develop, market and sell to business in today's tech landscape.

A basic definition of SaaS is a piece of software that is served from the company selling the software own servers. This is beyond the traditional method where a customer would install the software on their own server/s or computers. SaaS also represents a model where a company pays monthly or annual subscription for a piece of software that can either be installed locally or accessed through the cloud.

Some software as a service platform offers the software or service only through the seller’s own servers, while others offer both online and/or local means of being of accessing a particular SaaS.

There many SaaS platform types; they range from Finance to Customer Relation to Office Suite. Some of these types of service are:
<h2>Office Suite</h2>
<img width="300" height="225" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-256" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/ms-office-suite-300x225.png" />

This is one of the most popular types of SaaS, if not the highest grossing. It is an online office suite service that can be offered with or without an on-premise offering. There are many players vying to be the platform on which real office work is done.
<h3>Office 365</h3>
Office 365 from Microsoft, which is far and away the leader. It was not the first on the market, but it had the backing of Microsoft Office Suite legacy, the will Microsoft’s leadership and financial push of Microsoft’s very extensive cash war-chest. It currently has 120 million monthly active users. Although it is difficult to extract how much money is made by Office 365, it grew by 42% in revenue and 32% in users in first quarter of the 2018 fiscal year. Microsoft’s cloud services made 5 billion dollars in the same quarter. The next major player in Microsoft’s cloud services is Azure, which is said to be a billion dollars per quarter business. Therefore, a good estimate of its last quarterly is around 3.5 billion dollars.
<h3>G-Suite</h3>
G-Suite from Google is probably the most popular with the general consumer, small businesses, and schools. After all, it was Google through Google docs that really made online office suite reliable, productive and cool to use. Although it is popular with small business and casual consumers, its reach in the enterprise has been slowing due mostly to the aggressive approach Microsoft has taken with its own office suite SaaS.
<h3>Zoho Suite</h3>
Zoho Office Suite is a full-featured office suite SaaS from Zoho Corporation. I believe it to be the biggest threat to Office 365. It has all the features of Office 365 plus more exclusive features. The most important aspect of Zoho Office Suite is it freemium model. It offers the basic functionality for free, which is good enough to be productive with. If you are seeking enterprise services and security, only then you will need to pay
<h3>Quip</h3>
Quip is now owned by Salesforce.com. It is the newest serious competitor in this type of SaaS. With the backing of Salesforce.com, I believe that Quip can be a great player in online office suites, but today is not that time.
<h3>Customer Relationship Management (CRM)</h3>
<img width="300" height="296" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-217" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/benefits-of-crm-300x296.jpg" />

Customer Relationship Management is a SaaS that manages customer information, automate marketing, and track sales through the pipeline. There are many players in this SaaS sector; too many to mention. However, the clear leader is Salesforce.com.
<h3>Salesforce.com</h3>
Salesforce.com was born when some Oracle employees decided to rebel against the slow and bureaucratic technology giant. They made 8.9 billion dollars last fiscal year, and their current run rate is 10 billion dollars. Most of that money has come through CRM, making Salesforce.com the clear leader in CRM. Salesforce.com has a history of buying other companies and not just in CRM. Some the companies they are brought are Quip, Demandware, and ExactTarget.
<h3>SugarCRM</h3>
“All we do is CRM. It's in our name.” That is the motto of SugarCRM. SugarCRM enables businesses to create extraordinary customer relationships with the most empowering, adaptable and affordable customer relationship management (CRM) solution on the market. Recognized by leading market analysts as a CRM visionary and innovator, Sugar is deployed by more than 2 million individuals in over 120 countries and 26 languages.
<h3>Microsoft Dynamics CRM Online/Dynamics 365</h3>
Microsoft Dynamics CRM Online is Microsoft’s take on CRM. Dynamics CRM also has a client-side implication. Its latest implication it has become a part of Dynamics 365. Dynamics 365 is Microsoft’s all-in-one CRM and ERP suite that is borne in the cloud. The plan is to eventually replace the client-side CRM and ERP products. However, each of the online services has its on-premise counterpart. Its users and revenue are not reported by Microsoft. A safe bet is that it currently makes 250-500 million dollars per quarter.
<h3>Zoho CRM</h3>
Zoho is also involved in CRM and many other SaaS platforms. Zoho CRM is used by such companies such as Amazon India, Selectra, and SX Protection. It is perfectly integrated with its other SaaS applications and is included in its all-in-one plan called Zoho One. It is a very private company, therefore, it is hard to discover how much users and revenue its CRM offering has.
<h3>Pipedrive</h3>
Pipedrive is a sales management tool designed to help small sales teams manage intricate or lengthy sales processes. It was formed when its founders realized that the CRM landscape was populated by software designed to please the top brass while ignoring the needs of the people doing the actual selling. It is now used by over 50,000 companies around the world.
<h3>Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP)</h3>
<img width="300" height="245" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-219" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/ERP-300x245.jpg" />

ERP is the fraternal twin of CRM. It is the integrated management of core business process. It improves process efficiency and empowers information sharing across the organization, while giving management better insight into workflow and productivity, through the collection, storing, managing and interpreting of data from the many business activities of a company. This information is maintained by a database management system.
<h3>Sap S/4 HAHA</h3>
The leader in tradition ERP, SAP has made a successful transition to the cloud. It has done this through its own internal research and development and through acquisitions such as Concur Technologies, Success Factors, and Arbia. These acquisitions have allowed SAP to expand greatly beyond ERP SaaS; SAP is now a cloud company and not just an ERP cloud company. Its ERP cloud products follow a similar model to Microsoft’s; they can be pure-cloud or on-premise subscriptions. Sap offers its ERP products through what it calls S/4 HANA. S/4 HANA Cloud being the pure cloud offering for enterprise and midsize business, Business ByDesign being pure-cloud for midsize business, Business One is on-premise and cloud for lower midsize and small business, and S/4 HANA being on-premise and private cloud to be used by enterprise and midsize business. SAP ERP is their on-premise ERP product for those not ready for the cloud.
<h3>Microsoft Dynamics 365</h3>
As been mentioned above, Dynamics is Microsoft’s all-in-one ERP and CRM product. However, while Dynamics CRM has been online since 2011, a pure-cloud version of Dynamics ERP was only introduced in 2016. It is an actual hybrid service, where it can be in the cloud, on-premise or a mix of both. This is like most of Microsoft’s other SaaS software and services. ERP SaaS can be obtained from Microsoft through three basic methods. These methods are; Dynamics 365 Plan, Unified Operations Plan or by licensing the induvial applications namely Finance and Operations, Retail and Talent. Their on-premise counterpart is Operations server, which is accessed per subscriptions owned by the user.
<h3>Oracle/NetSuite</h3>
NetSuite was built on selling ERP SaaS; it does not do on-premise. It was founded in 1998, a month before Salesforce.com, making it the first ever cloud software company. NetSuite's services are aimed at small to medium-sized businesses, although their SaaS is offered to enterprise companies and can bring them benefits. Oracle Corporation purchased NetSuite for approximately $9.3 billion dollars in November 2016. It is one of the leading providers of cloud-based business management software. Its ERP is the most deployed ERP SaaS. Before it was bought by Oracle, it made $741 million dollars in revenue and $125 million dollars in profits, in 2015. Now it has given Oracle much needed clout in the important cloud software world. Its OneWorld product offers the kitchen sink in SaaS, from Finance to CRM and of course ERP.
<h3>Epicor</h3>
Epicor Software Corporation, a business software company based in Texas, was founded in 1972. Epicor helps organizations take advantage of the changing economic tide with its ERP suite. Epicor cloud ERP provides everything in one integrated system. Epicor ERP SaaS is delivered on-premise or it can be accessed through the Epicor cloud or a private cloud. It is mostly aimed at small to mid-size businesses, though it does try to be in the enterprise ERP market and starts at $175 per month. Epicor ERP has some more narrow focus such as Manufacturing, Distributors, Retailers and Service Providers. Besides ERP, Epicor is also involved in many of the other SaaS types, like most other companies doing SaaS.
<h3>Infor</h3>
Infor is a multi-national privately held enterprise software company, and it focuses on SaaS. Their offering includes financial systems, supply chain, CRM and of course ERP. Infor deploys its cloud applications through Amazon Web Services. Infor had around 58 million cloud users as of July 2016, as well as around 90,000 corporate customers overall. Infor specializes in specific industries such as Manufacturing, Distribution and Equipment and Services Industries. It can be deployed in the cloud, on-premise or hybrid. It claims that 19 of the top 20 A&amp;D companies, to 4 of 5 top brewers, to 5 of the top 10 global banks use it.
<h3>Collaboration</h3>
<img width="300" height="241" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-257" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/collaboration-software-new-300x241.png" />

Collaboration software is designed to help people involved in a common task to achieve their goals. They archive discussions and work history and make them searchable, which helps people learn from the past. Collaboration software comes in many forms, the most popular ones fall into the unified communication field, where you get all your communications needs in one place. Others are more specialized in chat or video/audio etc. This one of the most populated SaaS fields in terms of competitors.
<h3>Slack</h3>
Slack has been called the email killer. Slack is a chat-based platform that offers other services such as audio and video. Slack offers persistent chat rooms called channels, which are organized by topic, as well as private groups and direct messaging. All content inside Slack is searchable, including files, conversations, and people. It integrates with third-party services and allows the integration of community-built extension. Slack makes it possible for any user, group or teams to access it through a specific URL or invitation. It follows a freemium model, where it is very functional for free, much more storage, user, security and compliance and greater archiving are available for $8/user/month or $15/user month.
<h3>Microsoft Team/Skype for Business</h3>
Office 365 is the home to many collaboration services and software. Every single service in Microsoft’s SaaS armory is connected, from Dynamics 365 to Power BI. This means that it is easy for Microsoft to implement collaboration throughout its SaaS offering. In Office 365, if a group is formed in Outlook, that becomes a group in Yammer and Microsoft Team. If a document is shared through Skype for Business, it becomes apart of OneDrive for business. However, Skype for Business and Microsoft Teams are where collaboration lives. Skype for Business and Teams are very similar, in fact, Teams was created by the Skype team. It was created to be just a rival to Slack, but Microsoft has decided to rip all of Skype for Business features and implement in Teams; Teams has been a great success for them. Teams is a unified communication platform and when Microsoft is finished its services will range from chat to telephone dial-in for conferences and everything in between. Teams has a major advantage over many other collaborative SaaS because basically all its features come free with Office 365 and from the biggest name is Enterprise software.
<h3>Atlassian HipChat/Confluence</h3>
Atlassian is famous for its collaborative software and services. In 2004, it released Confluence, a team collaboration platform that lets users work together on projects, co-create content, and share documents and other media assets. HipChat is made for internal private online chat and instant messaging. It offers one-on-one and group/topic chat as well cloud-based file storage, video calling, searchable message history and inline-image viewing. The software is available to download on desktop or mobile. HipChat uses a freemium model, with the free model being very proficient. In September 2017 Atlassian replaced HipChat with a new cloud product called Stride, although HipChat continued on-premise with HipChat Data Center. Stride is just a Slack clone that more resemble Microsoft Teams.
<h3>Google Hangouts/Meet</h3>
Google Hangouts Meet is a new chat-based collaboration service from Google that is similar to Slack. It allows for the holding impromptu video meetings on the go, virtual training classes around the world, and remote interview. G-Suite Enterprise can host a Hangouts Meet video meeting for up to 50 users at a time and G Suite Basic and Business up to 25 participants. Meet, like Microsoft Teams, will eventually replace the classical Hangouts.
<h3>Zoho Connect</h3>
Connect is another outstanding offering from Zoho. It combines all the features of Slack, but add its own twists such as a section for company manuals, a forum and a project management service called Tasks. It is free to users and you only paid if you need extra features. It is a nice little SaaS from a nice company and exciting company.
<h3>Podio</h3>
Podio is a collaboration SaaS founded in 2009. It was acquired by Citrix in 2012. Podio is the all you can eat collaboration SaaS. Its communication is done through a Yammer-like private social network. It offers project management, CRM, and tasks.
<h3>GoToMeeting/Join.me</h3>
These are collaboration SaaS from LogMeIn. They offer very similar functionality, including toll-free audio, webinar, screen sharing, video conference and free conference call. Join.me is LogMeIn homegrown collaboration software, while GoToMeeting was obtained in 2016 when Citrix shun off the GoTo family of products.
<h3>Project Management</h3>
<img width="300" height="267" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-259" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/Workday-website-graphic5-1024x910-300x267.jpg" />

Project management SaaS is used to deliver projects on time and within budget. It allows teams to both work and collaborate on projects. Project management enables the creation of workspaces that allows team members and outside partners keep an eye on every detail that brings a project to fruition. They help teams handle common problems, such as slipped deadlines, by automatically rescheduling tasks that are affected by them. They allow team managers to see how work is on the plate of each team member, allowing the manager to reduce or increase workload. They can also track time spent on projects and allows for integration into other services such finance, billing, accounts and invoicing.
<h3>Zoho Projects</h3>
Zoho Projects is a project management SaaS from the venerable Zoho Corporation. It is considered the leader in project management. It offers a fully functional free plan, with a paid only necessary for additional support and features like storage. The paid plan begins at $25 per month which grants 20 projects and 10gb of storage with unlimited user access. A team can grow into a higher tier plan as their needs changes.
<h3>Trello</h3>
Trello was launched in 2011 by Fog Creek. In July 2014, Trello was span off from Fog Creek to form Trello Inc and in 2017, it was acquired by Atlassian. Trello describes itself as having a board that is a list of lists, filled with cards. Trello has everything you will need to organize projects of any size. In each card you can add comments, upload file attachments, create checklists, labels, due dates and much more. It allows you to invite anyone to your board for free and it is easy to assign tasks. It is freemium offering with its free version being free forever with unlimited boards, lists, cards, members, checklists, and attachments. There is a 10MB limit for uploading files, though a file of any size can be linked through a cloud storage service. It Business Class plan is priced at $9.99/user/month with additional storage and features like app integration. The Enterprise plan is for $20.83/user/month or less for additional compliance and security.
<h3>Asana</h3>
Asana is a SaaS that aims to improve team collaboration. It has a vision of having users managing projects and tasks online without the use of email. Each team can create a workspace, which contains projects, and projects contain tasks. In each task, users can add notes, comments, attachments, and tags. Organizations is an Asana product that is aimed at the enterprise. Organizations added an Asana Team Browser as well tools that the enterprise might demand such as auto-join. It is used by companies like Deloitte, Allstate, General Electric, Redbull, and Airbnb. Asana is available for free with unlimited tasks, projects, and conversations with up to 15 team members. The paid plan starts $9.99/user/month and offers features such as unlimited dashboards, advanced search and reporting and private teams and projects. The enterprise plan is customizable and offers additional compliance and security.
<h3>Wrike</h3>
Wrike is a project management SaaS. It allows users to manage and track projects, deadlines, schedules, and other workflow processes. Write also enable the collaboration of users for better communication. In 2016, it was used by over 12,000 companies. Wrike helps teams track dates and dependencies associated with projects, manage assignments and resources, and track time. Collaboration features include the Wrike's Live co-editor, discussion threads on tasks, and tools for attaching documents, editing them, and tracking their changes. Wrike offers integration with other systems, which enable users to easily have all the information needed for a project in one place. Integrations include Google, Microsoft, Adobe Creative Cloud, Box, GitHub, and Jira. Wrike can be had for free with up to 5 users. This includes cloud integrations and 2Gb of storage. The professional plan for $9.80/user/month is for 5, 10, 15 users. It comes with 5Gb of storage and 15Gb of uploads per month. $24.80/user/month is for the business plan, which grants report templates, time tracking and salesforce integration for 5-200 users. The Marketers plan for 5-unlimited users cost 34.60/user/month and includes video proofing, tailored workspace, and Adobe Creative Cloud Extension. Its unlimited user Enterprise plan is custom and tailored to each company.
<h3>Jira</h3>
Jira is a project management SaaS developed for agile teams. It is used for issue tracking, project management, and bug tracking by over 75,000 customers according to its parent Atlassian. It at time one or another been used by Hibernate, Twitter, Skype Technologies, NASA and the United States Department of Defense. Jira comes in three packages: Core, Software and Service Desk. Jira Software is built specifically for software teams. It combines powerful developer tool integrations with important features and functionality required for great agile software development. Service Desk is built for IT and service teams, providing them with everything they need for out-of-the-box incident, problem, and change management. While Core is a simplified project management tool for customers looking to extend the power of Jira to their organization. It can be hosted on Jira’s own cloud or deployed on a customer’s own private cloud through the Jira Software Server. Pricing for Jira starts at $10/month for up to 10 users. For 11-100 users, the price is $7/user/month. The average price per user decreases as more users are added to the plan.
<h3>Workfront</h3>
Workfront is a work management and project management SaaS company. It features enterprise work management, issue tracking, document management time tracking and portfolio management. Workfront is used by some very important enterprises such as Cisco Systems, Comcast, Food and Drug Administration and National Geographic. With Workfront, teams receive requests in a standardized format and this makes the manager’s job easier. It starts at $ 30/user/ month, but its cost varies according to the amount users that need the project management service.
<h3>Accounting/Billing and Invoicing/ Transaction Processing</h3>
<img width="288" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-218" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/Depositphotos_24482707_m-e1513026779372-288x300.jpg" />

<img width="1" height="1" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-298" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/1money.png" />This is a type SaaS that deals with the accounting of money. Many of the SaaS that offers Accounting, also comes with functionality such as Billing, Invoicing, Booking and Transaction Processing. While others just offer one or more service(s), like PayPal only offering Transaction Processing and Invoicing. Some common modules of accounting/financial SaaS are accounts payable, accounts receivable, general ledger, payroll, and trial balance. Accounting software was once dominated by the traditional on-premise, buy-once model; however, every new player has been borne in the cloud, and this new subscription model has been met with rapid adoption. This has forced traditional players to put out their own SaaS offering.
<h3>PayPal</h3>
PayPal is a worldwide online payments system company that supports online money transfers and serves through SaaS platform. PayPal is one of the world's largest, most reputable and most famous Internet payment companies. They make money by charging a fee for the processing of payments for online vendors, auction and other e-commerce users and businesses. PayPal allows consumers and merchants to receive money in more than 100 currencies, withdraw funds in 56 currencies and hold balances a PayPal accounts in 25 currencies. PayPal services include PayPal for payment transactions, PayPal Credit offers loans to businesses, Venmo is a mobile payment service and Braintree helps businesses of all sizes accept and process payment. They also offer a $30 per month business account along with its free business and personal accounts.
During its fiscal year 2017 third quarter, its sated some of its highlights were:
<ul>
 	<li>8.2 million active customer accounts added, with net new actives up 88%.</li>
 	<li>218 million active customer accounts, with more than 17 million merchant (business) accounts.</li>
 	<li>1.9 billion payment transactions, up 26%.</li>
 	<li>32.8 payment transactions per active account on a trailing twelve months basis, up 9%. $114 billion in total payment volume, up 30%.</li>
 	<li>Revenue of $3.239 billion, up 21%.</li>
 	<li>Net income of $530 million, up 33%.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Workday</h3>
Workday is a financial management and human capital management SaaS company. The company delivers unified human capital management, management, payroll and financial management solutions. Workday provides the hardware and middleware to run its services; it installs and maintains the installation, and guarantee uptime. Workday offers a custom pricing structure based on the needs of the company requiring their services. In their fiscal year 2018 third quarter result, they reported total revenues of $555.4 million, an increase of 34.3%. Operating loss was $80.1 million, compared to an operating loss of $105.9 million last year.
<h3>Sage Intacct</h3>
Intacct is an enterprise-class general ledger accounting platform operating on top of an Oracle database. Intacct offers custom pricing based on the needs of its business customer.

Intacct describes its core products thus:
<h6>General ledger</h6>
The general ledger is the heart of financial management system. Sage Intacct's general ledger was built to be different, bringing you greater visibility, scalability, and flexibility.
<h6>Accounts payable</h6>
Manage the entire accounts payable process with newfound speed and efficiency.
<h6>Purchasing</h6>
Ensure your purchasing team is able to place the right orders at the right time for the right
price.
<h6>Order management</h6>
Handle higher order volumes, processing complexity, and pricing structures. All while saving time and improving profitability.
<h6>Accounts receivable</h6>
Fast, efficient accounts receivable management, you can improve customer satisfaction and accelerate your cash cycle.
<h6>Cash management</h6>
A complete picture of a company’s cash and working capital, without using spreadsheets to track balances and transactions.
<h6>Reporting and dashboards</h6>
Enables a company to derive better insights from the valuable information in the core financials. Sage Intacct tracks operational and financial data—by business driver—to give businesses superior reporting power and a more meaningful view of your whole business.
<h6>Digital Board Book</h6>
Make quicker, more strategic decisions with real-time SaaS metrics that include operational metrics.
<h6>Collaborate</h6>
Handle communication between departments quickly, efficiently, and effectively with a secure social layer embedded in a company’s Sage Intacct financial management system
<h3>QuickBooks</h3>
QuickBooks is an accounting SaaS from Intuit, that is mainly aimed at small and medium-size businesses. Its services include remote access capabilities, remote payroll assistance and outsourcing, electronic payment functions, invoicing, inventory management online banking and reconciliation, mapping features with Google Maps, marketing options through Google, and e-mail functionality through Microsoft Outlook and Outlook Express. Although it has heavily promoted it online QuickBooks service, it still has a dedicated desktop version. QuickBooks pricing is based on the features required by a business. The plans are: Self-employed for $10/month, Simple Start for $15/month, Essentials for $35/month, and Plus for $50/month.
<h3>Zoho Books</h3>
Zoho Books is an accounting software from Zoho Corporation. The core features are Estimates, Time Tracking, Expense Tracking, Client Portal, Financial Reports, Accountant, Banking and Credit Notes. Zoho Books has three main plans; Basic is for $9/month, which comes with all the core features plus 5 Work Flows rules. The standard plan costs $19/month and comes with all the features of the basic plan plus Bills, Vendor Credits, Reporting Tags, and 10 rules per module in Work Rules. The professional plan comes with Purchase Order, Sales Order, and Inventory, in addition to all the features of Standard. All the plans offer integration with Zoho’s other products.
<h3>Xero</h3>
Xero states that it is a cloud-based accounting software connects people with the right numbers anytime, anywhere, on any device. For accountants and bookkeepers, Xero helps build a trusted relationship with small business clients through online collaboration. They have over 1 million subscribers. It features include automatic bank and credit card account feeds, invoicing, accounts payable, expense claims, fixed asset depreciation, purchase orders, and standard business and management reporting. Xero has three plans. The Starter plan starts at $9/month and allows users to send 5 invoices and quotas, reconcile up to 20 bank transactions and enter 5 bills. The Standard plan allows for unlimited invoices and quotas, unlimited bank transactions reconciliations, unlimited bill recordings, and payroll for up to 5 people. It costs $30/month. The last plan is the Premium and starts at $70/month for all the features of Standard plus payroll for up to 10 people and multicurrency. It goes up to $180/month for payroll for 100 people.
<h3>Email Marketing Software</h3>
<img width="298" height="300" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-339" alt="" src="http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/business-email-lists-298x300.jpg" />

Email Marketing Software SaaS is used to automate email marketing and relationship building allowing for the optimization of message delivery.
<h3>MailChimp</h3>
MailChimp which can be had for free, $10/month for Growing Business and $199/month for the Pro Marketer plan.
<h3>Freshmail</h3>
Freshmail is priced based on the number of subscribers. It ranges from $14/month for 1000 subscribers to $405/month for 100,000 subscribers. These plans allow for unlimited emails to subscribers. A user can also pay according to the amount of email it wants to send. 5000 emails would cost $30 and 1,000,000 emails would cost $1300.
<h3>Campaign Monitor</h3>
Campaign Monitor starts with the Basic plan at $9/month for 2500 emails across its campaigns program and automated emails. For $29/month, a business can send unlimited email through the Unlimited plan. $149/month gives you the Premier plan which offers optimization and further compliance. There is also a 1:1 personalization Advanced plan.
<h3>Autopilot</h3>
Autopilot Base plan is for $20/month and comes with:
<ul>
 	<li>Unlimited Journeys</li>
 	<li>Emails, Headsup, SMS</li>
 	<li>Segments &amp; Reporting</li>
 	<li>Slack &amp; Zapier Integration</li>
</ul>
The Business plan for $40/month comes with all the features of the Base plan in addition to:
<ul>
 	<li>Salesforce Integration</li>
 	<li>Segment.com &amp; API Access</li>
 	<li>A/B Split Testing</li>
 	<li>Journey Reviews</li>
</ul>
<h3>iContact</h3>
iContact comes in two plans. The first one is Essential $32/month when billed annually. It features:
<ul>
 	<li>Drag-and-Drop Editing</li>
 	<li>A/B Testing</li>
 	<li>Live Customer Support</li>
 	<li>Google Analytics</li>
 	<li>Reliable Sending</li>
 	<li>List Management</li>
 	<li>Autoresponders</li>
 	<li>Mobile-focused Design</li>
 	<li>Campaign Tracking</li>
 	<li>Social Media Sharing/Posting</li>
 	<li>PDF Links</li>
 	<li>API Support</li>
 	<li>Custom Design Work</li>
 	<li>Multiple Users</li>
 	<li>Multiple Folders</li>
 	<li>Onboarding Advice</li>
</ul>
The Professional plan is for $99/month. It has all Essential features plus:
<ul>
 	<li>Workflows</li>
 	<li>Triggered Messages</li>
 	<li>Landing Pages</li>
 	<li>Engagement Tracking</li>
 	<li>Behavioral Targeting</li>
 	<li>Social Monitoring</li>
 	<li>Funnel Reports</li>
 	<li>Custom Objects</li>
</ul>
<h3>Closing</h3>
There are clear leaders appearing in the field of SaaS namely: Salesforce.com, Google, Sap Inc, Zoho Corporation, Paypal. When combined, however, Microsoft is the leader when it comes to revenue and active users. It is also one of the most represented in all the subcategories along with Zoho. It has the clearest documentation, which I think is vital. Its war chest is the biggest, with only Google anywhere near. However, the game has only just started, and the winner will be difficult to predict.

.[maxbutton id="1" ]

[amazon_link asins='1546308490,0984881247,0988830809,1119046580,1503534537,0986019526,0321350170,B01FIW1JE0' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-2' marketplace='US' link_id='484707f4-deb9-11e7-8792-6335693d193f']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>231</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-12-11 20:55:02]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-11 20:55:02]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[software-as-a-service-saas]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="cloud-services"><![CDATA[Cloud Services]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="microsoft"><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="office-365"><![CDATA[Office 365]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="software-as-a-service"><![CDATA[Software As A Service]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[30]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[23]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[261]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yst_is_cornerstone]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_focuskw_text_input]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[SaaS]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_focuskw]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[SaaS]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_metadesc]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Software as a Service(SaaS) is a cornerstone of today's technology world and every company worth its salt is fighting to win in SaaS.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_linkdex]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[83]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6343399368]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_old_slug]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[software-service-saas]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_page_template]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[top_ten_list]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Top 10 Weapons So Deadly They Are Prohibited</title>
		<link>http://msftworld.ml/2017/12/top10-banned-weapons/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[revben]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://msftworld.ml/?p=270</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[&nbsp;

War is a bloody business, where the most devastating weapons are used to take life. However, most of our leaders who take us into war will tell us that wars fought for reasons like oil, land, and love, are not carried out to cause excessive hurt. To prove this, many countries have signed agreements to ban some of the most harmful weapons to prohibit them on the battlefield. Here are the Top 10 deadliest Weapons that are Prohibited.

[amazon_link asins='B071QY1WLY,1465450963,B011CRO9IS,1847327109,1626164533,1861896514,B01M4GGW4Z,1465436022,B000NI7PQG,0465054935' template='ProductCarousel' store='us-1' marketplace='US' link_id='ffd6fe8e-deeb-11e7-a155-2548bcc2f145']]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>270</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date><![CDATA[2017-12-12 03:15:08]]></wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt><![CDATA[2017-12-12 03:15:08]]></wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status><![CDATA[open]]></wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name><![CDATA[top10-banned-weapons]]></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type><![CDATA[post]]></wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password><![CDATA[]]></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="non-tech"><![CDATA[Non-Tech]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="top-10-list"><![CDATA[Top 10 List]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_edit_last]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_thumbnail_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[272]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wp_page_template]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_quads_config_visibility]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:0:{}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yst_is_cornerstone]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_focuskw_text_input]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Weapons]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_focuskw]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Weapons]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_title]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Top 10 Weapons So Dangerous, They Are Banned]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_linkdex]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[25]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_content_score]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[90]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_yoast_wpseo_primary_category]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[25]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[dsq_thread_id]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6343891060]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wplp_post_front]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wplp_post_tag]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wplp_post_archive]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wplp_post_feed]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wplp_post_recent]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[_wplp_post_rel]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[top_ten_list]]></wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:10:{i:0;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:18:"Biological Weapons";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:76:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/10-terrifying-bio-weapons.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"274";s:7:"content";s:1297:"A biological weapon is a living organism like bacteria or viruses that can be used to cause death or disease on a huge scale. Biological weapons have long been used in wars. In the Middle Ages, bubonic plague victims who had died were thrown over walls in enemy lands in an attempt to spread the disease. Then, more recently in 2001, anthrax was delivered by mail to U.S. media and government offices, resulting in five deaths. Anthrax is one of the deadliest biological weapons in the world. It can be transmitted through skin contact or inhalation. Symptoms include fever, respiratory problems, fatigue, muscle aches, enlarged lymph nodes, nausea, vomiting, diarrhea and black ulcers. It's treated with the use of antibiotics and it can be prevented with the use of vaccines.

There are numerous more options for those looking to create a biological weapon, with the infectiousness being an important factor in determining how quickly the weapon can spread and cause harm. Obviously, these weapons are torturous for those infected, which is why in 1972 there was an international consensus to ban them, under the Biological and Toxin Weapons Convention. It prohibits the development, production, and stockpiling of biological and toxin weapons, though it has no governing body to enforce compl";}i:1;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:20:"Blinding Laser Beams";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:56:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/Lazer.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"275";s:7:"content";s:865:"If you've ever played a science fiction video game or enjoy Star Wars, you'd be very familiar with laser beam weapons. But now, what was once science fiction has become reality. Thanks to a tone of money spent on research and development over the past few decades, laser beams have now become powerful enough to use on the battlefield, with devastating effects. The US Navy’s Laser Weapon System, (LAWS), looks like a small telescope. It can track a moving target and fire a steady laser beam strong enough to burn a hole through steel. With a weapon, made of light and not bullets, running out of ammunition would be a distant possibility. Although they have just started to be viable, they have been banned preemptively because of their potential to blind combatants or civilians, which is seen as inhumane when compared to putting a bullet through their heads.";}i:2;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:12:"Punji Sticks";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:69:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/chu.chi4-17march13.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"291";s:7:"content";s:1110:"Punji sticks are sharpened pieces of bamboo, which are between one and two feet. Fire is used to harden the point to ensure they are extremely pointed for a long period of time. Poison or animal excreta are normally used to make the sticks far deadlier. Although their ability to cause hurt or even death was great, they were very simple to make. This meant that they were produced in great quantity during the Vietnam War, where they became known to the world.

During the Vietnam War, the Viet Cong was at disadvantage against the better equipped American led forces. This strife led to the creation of the punji sticks. Punji became so fearsome, that American soldiers were sometimes more fearful of losing their feet than getting shot. They were not designed to be fatal, but rather to seriously wound a soldier, so that one or two other soldiers would be needed to take the wounded soldier off the battlefield, thus getting of all three of them in one blow. Even if a soldier were not wounded, he would be far too cautious in battle. Punji sticks are banned from use as weaponry under the 1980 Geneva Co";}i:3;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:18:"Incendiary Weapons";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:63:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/flamethrower.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"277";s:7:"content";s:857:"Incendiary weapons are mass destruction beasts that produce fire through some type of chemical reaction. They are designed to burn or set fire to large areas, many of which contain civilians. There are over 180 types of incendiary weapons, with most famous being Napalm and white phosphorus. Napalm was used with harrowing effects during the Vietnam war. This lead to the inclusion of Incendiary weapons in the 1980 Convention on Certain Conventional Weapons treaty. Actual flame, heat or chemical reactions weapons are banned under the treaty, which means flamethrowers can only be used when civilians are not in an area. Despite the treaty, many nations are still producing, stockpiling and using. The U.S. is alleged to have used white phosphorus in Afghanistan and Iraq. Although it is not on the ban list, it is clearly being used an incendiary weapon.";}i:4;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:14:"Brass Knuckles";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:167:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/Solid-Brass-Knuckle-Duster-brass-knuckles-WeaponCollector-homemade-home-made-hand-handmade-weaponcollector-custom-11.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"278";s:7:"content";s:657:"Some people might see brass knuckles as a fashion statement, however, injuries from brass knuckles can be serious, as the weapons are composed of hardened material like brass, chrome, or hard plastic. Brass knuckles can inflict broken bones, cuts, concussions, and eye injuries. In World War I and II, brass knuckles were often attached to knives for use in trench warfare. They are legal in many states but are outright banned in California, Michigan, Illinois, and Vermont. Other states only ban metallic brass knuckles or apply age restrictions to ownership of them. However, most states classify brass knuckles as concealed weapons that require permits.";}i:5;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:18:"Mininum Metal Mine";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:92:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/Defense.gov_News_Photo_970710-N-2240H-004.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"279";s:7:"content";s:999:"One of the most unexpected and brutal ways one can meet their end is by a landmine. One of the most horrifying types of landmine is those with non-detectable fragments. Even if a person is not killed by the mine, but a non-detectable fragment enters their body, they could still be in big trouble. This is because X-ray cannot detect these fragments and the surgeons are forced to operate blindly; searching through the patient’s body by hand. These mines are called minimum metal mine as they use the least amount of metal possible. The substitute for metal can be plastic, wood or glass; with only parts like the fuse using metal. Everyone agrees that minimum metal mines should be banned, however, most of the world also agrees that all mines should be banned. This was done through the treaty called Convention on the Prohibition of the Use, Stockpiling, Production and Transfer of Anti-Personnel Mines and on their Destruction. Only 34 states are not signatories, including U.S.A. and Russia.";}i:6;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:24:"Three-Sided Trench Knife";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:57:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/587A_2.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"280";s:7:"content";s:722:"Trench knives are designed to kill or gravely incapacitate an enemy soldier at close quarters. It was developed in response to a need for a close combat weapon for soldiers conducting assaults and raids on enemy trenches during World War 1. An example of a World War I trench knife is the German Army's Nahkampfmesser. The Axis, during World War 2 widely issued the Nahkampfmesser and designs developed from it to the ordinary soldier as general-purpose fighting and utility knives. The Allied armies restricted issue of trench knives to elite infantry units and infantry not otherwise equipped with the bayonet. These knives are banned by the Geneva Convention because they left nasty wounds that couldn't be stitched up.";}i:7;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:36:"Expanding Ordnance /Poisoned Bullets";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:62:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/hst-bullets.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"281";s:7:"content";s:832:"Expanding Ordnances are projectiles that expand on impact, increasing in diameter to limit penetration to produce a faster incapacitation. One type of expanding ordnances is hollow point bullets. Otherwise called dum-dums, they were used by Olympian Oscar Pistorius to kill his girlfriend. Although they were legal for him to own, they were banned from international warfare in 1899. Police forces are still allowed to use them as they do not normally leave the body to injure bystanders. Expanding bullets are not the only banned ammo type; poison bullets are also banned. If someone is shot by a poison bullet, they not only have to worry about the wound but also the possibility of a secondary infection. Lead is a type of poison bullet that is still used to hunt wild animals, though efforts are being made to ban that practice.";}i:8;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:13:"Certain Bombs";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:109:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/The-Difference-Between-A-Hydrogen-And-Atomic-Bomb-featured.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"282";s:7:"content";s:1418:"In war, a bomb can be one of the most effective means of removing the enemies’ souls from their body. Bombs are a staple of war, but not all of them are welcomed. One such bomb is the cluster bomb. When they are exploded, they release many projectiles to injure or damage combatants and vehicles. In a 2008 Convention on Cluster Munitions, they were banned because they have a wide area of effect and more importantly they leave behind a large number of dangerous unexploded ordnances. Another banned bomb are dirty bombs, which are loaded with radioactive material. Due to the nuclear materials in them, they are not normally used in war as they turn the battlefield into a nuclear wasteland. Never less, they are banned by international war. The most destructive agent of war humans has ever created is the nuclear bomb.

During the Second World War, nuclear bombs were used for only first and second times ever on the Japanese cities of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. These bombs killed a combined 200,000 people. The destructive potential of nuclear weapons has led to the Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons, where only a hand full of nations are allowed to stockpile them. Today, only Russia, France, China, the United Kingdom, U.S.A, Pakistan, India, and Israel legally own nuclear weapons. A new treaty called the Treaty on the Prohibition of Nuclear Weapons, calls for a complete ban on nuclear we";}i:9;a:5:{s:5:"title";s:16:"Chemical Weapons";s:5:"image";s:0:"";s:9:"image_url";s:92:"http://msftworld.ml/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/160815095344-chemical-weapons-super-tease.jpg";s:8:"image_id";s:3:"283";s:7:"content";s:2049:"Chemical weapons are some of the most inhumane ways you can take someone’s life. They are so hated, that many wars have been started in the guise of getting rid of them. One chemical weapon is mustard gas that was used in World War 1 to burn the skin of combatants. A gas mask could not protect against it and the long effects were brutal. Another dangerous gas is Sarin, which is colorless, tasteless and has no odor in its pure form. Symptoms include a runny nose, eye pain, drooling, excessive sweating and rapid breathing. Assad is alleged to have used it in 2017 to kill nearly 80 people. Phosgene was also widely used in the first World War and was responsible for three-quarters of all gas fatalities. Its caused major lung damage and suffocation in its victim and death soon followed in many cases. Tear gas is a common utility for many people in modern times, however, it cannot be used in war like all other chemical weapons.

At the Kuala Lumpur International Airport on February 13, Kim Jong Un sent his assassins to kill his half-brother, Kim Jong Nam, using venomous agent x, VX, for short. VX is an extremely toxic synthetic thiophosphate. These agents severely disrupt the body's signaling between the nervous and muscular systems. This leads to a prolonged neuromuscular blockade, flaccid paralysis of all the muscles in the body and death by asphyxiation. It is banned by the Chemical Weapons Convention of 1993, where production and stockpiling of VX exceeding 100 grams per year is outlawed. VX can cause death in minutes, however, there exists another nerve agent that is five to eight times more potent than VX; it is called Novichok agent. They were developed by the Soviet Union is the 1970s and 1980s. Its main goals were to be undetectable by NATO while bypassing NATO’s protective gear.

Do you think these banned weapons have made war any safer? Which of these weapons do you fear the most? Is there any other weapon you think should be banned? Or do you hate all weapons? Leave your answer in the comments sectio";}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
